[
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iku'?",
    "Answer": "go"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'see'?",
    "Answer": "miru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q3",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ooi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "a lot of",
      "many"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q4",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'home'?",
    "Answer": "ie"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q5",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'this'?",
    "Answer": "kore"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q6",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sore'?",
    "Answer": [
      "that",
      "that one"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q7",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'I'?",
    "Answer": "watashi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q8",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shigoto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "work",
      "job"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q9",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itsu'?",
    "Answer": "when"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q10",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'do'?",
    "Answer": "suru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q11",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'deru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "go out",
      "leave"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q12",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'use'?",
    "Answer": "tsukau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q13",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'place'?",
    "Answer": "tokoro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q14",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsukuru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "make",
      "create"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q15",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'omou'?",
    "Answer": "think"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q16",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'have'?",
    "Answer": "motsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q17",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'buy'?",
    "Answer": "kau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q18",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'time'?",
    "Answer": "jikan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q19",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'know'?",
    "Answer": "shiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q20",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'onaji'?",
    "Answer": [
      "same",
      "identical"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q21",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ima'?",
    "Answer": "now"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q22",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atarashii'?",
    "Answer": "new"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q23",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naru'?",
    "Answer": "become"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q24",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(not) yet'?",
    "Answer": "mada"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q25",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'after'?",
    "Answer": "ato"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q26",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kiku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hear",
      "ask"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q27",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'say'?",
    "Answer": "iu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q28",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sukunai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "few",
      "little"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q29",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'takai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "high",
      "tall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q30",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'child'?",
    "Answer": "kodomo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q31",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'so'?",
    "Answer": "sou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q32",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'already'?",
    "Answer": "mou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q33",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'student'?",
    "Answer": "gakusei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q34",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atsui'?",
    "Answer": "hot (to touch)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q35",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'douzo'?",
    "Answer": "please"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q36",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gogo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "afternoon",
      "p.m."
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q37",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'long'?",
    "Answer": "nagai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q38",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'book'?",
    "Answer": "hon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q39",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kotoshi'?",
    "Answer": "this year (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q40",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "often",
      "well"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q41",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanojo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "she",
      "oneâ€™s girlfriend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q42",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'how'?",
    "Answer": "dou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q43",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kotoba'?",
    "Answer": [
      "word",
      "language"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q44",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'face'?",
    "Answer": "kao"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q45",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'owaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "finish",
      "end"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q46",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hitotsu'?",
    "Answer": "one (thing)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q47",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'give'?",
    "Answer": "ageru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q48",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "like this",
      "such"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q49",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gakkou'?",
    "Answer": "school"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q50",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be given'?",
    "Answer": "kureru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q51",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'start (something)'?",
    "Answer": "hajimeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q52",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "get up",
      "get out of bed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q53",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'spring'?",
    "Answer": "haru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q54",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gozen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "morning",
      "a.m."
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q55",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'another'?",
    "Answer": "betsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q56",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'where'?",
    "Answer": "doko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q57",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'room'?",
    "Answer": "heya"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q58",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'young'?",
    "Answer": "wakai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q59",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'car'?",
    "Answer": "kuruma"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q60",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "put",
      "place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q61",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sumu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "live",
      "reside"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q62",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hataraku'?",
    "Answer": "work"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q63",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'muzukashii'?",
    "Answer": "difficult"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q64",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'teacher'?",
    "Answer": "sensei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q65",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stand'?",
    "Answer": "tatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q66",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yobu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "call",
      "name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q67",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'daigaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "university",
      "college"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q68",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yasui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "cheap",
      "inexpensive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q69",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'motto'?",
    "Answer": "more"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q70",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'go back home'?",
    "Answer": "kaeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q71",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wakaru'?",
    "Answer": "understand"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q72",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hiroi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "wide",
      "big"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q73",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suu'?",
    "Answer": "number"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q74",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'near'?",
    "Answer": "chikai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q75",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'there'?",
    "Answer": "soko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q76",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'run'?",
    "Answer": "hashiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q77",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'put in'?",
    "Answer": "ireru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q78",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'teach'?",
    "Answer": "oshieru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q79",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'aruku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "walk",
      "go on foot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q80",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'au'?",
    "Answer": "meet"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q81",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'write'?",
    "Answer": "kaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q82",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'head'?",
    "Answer": "atama"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q83",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sell'?",
    "Answer": "uru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q84",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'like (something) a lot'?",
    "Answer": "daisuki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q85",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'karada'?",
    "Answer": [
      "body",
      "physique"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q86",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'at once'?",
    "Answer": "sugu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q87",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fly'?",
    "Answer": "tobu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q88",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'totemo'?",
    "Answer": "very (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q89",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'who'?",
    "Answer": "dare"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q90",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'favorite'?",
    "Answer": "suki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q91",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yomu'?",
    "Answer": "read"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q92",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'next'?",
    "Answer": "tsugi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q93",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'you'?",
    "Answer": "anata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q94",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nomu'?",
    "Answer": "drink"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q95",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'furui'?",
    "Answer": "old"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q96",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'question'?",
    "Answer": "shitsumon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q97",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyou'?",
    "Answer": "today (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q98",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'friend'?",
    "Answer": "tomodachi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q99",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hayai'?",
    "Answer": "early"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q100",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'what'?",
    "Answer": "dore"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q101",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'beautiful'?",
    "Answer": "utsukushii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q102",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itsumo'?",
    "Answer": "always (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q103",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'leg'?",
    "Answer": "ashi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q104",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wake (someone) up'?",
    "Answer": "okosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q105",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'miseru'?",
    "Answer": "show"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q106",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'musume'?",
    "Answer": [
      "daughter",
      "girl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q107",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'enjoy'?",
    "Answer": "tanoshimu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q108",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'color'?",
    "Answer": "iro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q109",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'minna'?",
    "Answer": "everybody (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q110",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "take",
      "get"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q111",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'study'?",
    "Answer": "benkyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q112",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dekiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "can do",
      "be good at"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q113",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'short'?",
    "Answer": "mijikai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q114",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ochiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fall",
      "come down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q115",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'musuko'?",
    "Answer": "son"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q116",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiroi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "white",
      "blank"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q117",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'airplane'?",
    "Answer": "hikouki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q118",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'byouki'?",
    "Answer": "illness"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q119",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fuyu'?",
    "Answer": "winter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q120",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toshi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "year",
      "age"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q121",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'omoi'?",
    "Answer": "heavy"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q122",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mune'?",
    "Answer": [
      "chest",
      "breast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q123",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'harau'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pay (money",
      "respect",
      "attention",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q124",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'karui'?",
    "Answer": "light (of weight)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q125",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'find'?",
    "Answer": "mitsukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q126",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wasureru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "forget",
      "leave behind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q127",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'alcohol'?",
    "Answer": "sake"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q128",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'which (polite)'?",
    "Answer": "dochira"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q129",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ane'?",
    "Answer": "(oneâ€™s own) older sister"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q130",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oboeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "memorize",
      "learn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q131",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'semai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "narrow",
      "small"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q132",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'akai'?",
    "Answer": "red"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q133",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wear'?",
    "Answer": "kiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q134",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'laugh'?",
    "Answer": "warau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q135",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'most'?",
    "Answer": "ichiban"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q136",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'class session'?",
    "Answer": "jugyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q137",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'week'?",
    "Answer": "shuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q138",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Chinese character'?",
    "Answer": "kanji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q139",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bicycle'?",
    "Answer": "jitensha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q140",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'train'?",
    "Answer": "densha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q141",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'search for'?",
    "Answer": "sagasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q142",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kami'?",
    "Answer": "paper"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q143",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'utau'?",
    "Answer": "sing"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q144",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'osoi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "slow",
      "late"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q145",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kubi'?",
    "Answer": "neck"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q146",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fast'?",
    "Answer": "hayai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q147",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'issho ni'?",
    "Answer": [
      "together",
      "at the same time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q148",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kongetsu'?",
    "Answer": "this month"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q149",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'play'?",
    "Answer": "asobu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q150",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'far'?",
    "Answer": "tooi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q151",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'weak'?",
    "Answer": "yowai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q152",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ear'?",
    "Answer": "mimi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q153",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sit'?",
    "Answer": "suwaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q154",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'right'?",
    "Answer": "migi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q155",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'abiru'?",
    "Answer": "take (a shower)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q156",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shoulder'?",
    "Answer": "kata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q157",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'neru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "lie down and sleep",
      "go to sleep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q158",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'switch off'?",
    "Answer": "kesu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q159",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'genki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "healthy",
      "energetic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q160",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zenbu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "all",
      "whole"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q161",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'last year (colloquial)'?",
    "Answer": "kyonen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q162",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hiku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "draw",
      "pull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q163",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toshokan'?",
    "Answer": "library"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q164",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'raise'?",
    "Answer": "ageru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q165",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'midori'?",
    "Answer": "green"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q166",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ude'?",
    "Answer": "arm"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q167",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'doa'?",
    "Answer": "door (loan word)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q168",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'little girl'?",
    "Answer": "onna no ko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q169",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'boy'?",
    "Answer": "otoko no ko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q170",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'we (colloquial)'?",
    "Answer": "watashitachi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q171",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chikaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "near",
      "close to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q172",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "do",
      "give"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q173",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fairly'?",
    "Answer": "kanari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q174",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kuni'?",
    "Answer": "country"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q175",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okoru'?",
    "Answer": "happen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q176",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'autumn'?",
    "Answer": "aki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q177",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'send'?",
    "Answer": "okuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q178",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'die'?",
    "Answer": "shinu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q179",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'feeling'?",
    "Answer": "kimochi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q180",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'noru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "ride",
      "take"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q181",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be present",
      "stay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q182",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tree'?",
    "Answer": "ki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q183",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'open'?",
    "Answer": "akeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q184",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shimeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "shut",
      "close (doors",
      "windows",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q185",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuzuku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "continue",
      "follow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q186",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'doctor (polite)'?",
    "Answer": "oishasan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q187",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Japanese yen'?",
    "Answer": "en"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q188",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koko'?",
    "Answer": "here"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q189",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'matsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "wait",
      "wait for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q190",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hikui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "low",
      "short"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q191",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'receive'?",
    "Answer": "morau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q192",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'eat'?",
    "Answer": "taberu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q193",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ani'?",
    "Answer": "(oneâ€™s own) older brother"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q194",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'name'?",
    "Answer": "namae"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q195",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'husband'?",
    "Answer": "otto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q196",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ichi'?",
    "Answer": "one"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q197",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kekkon'?",
    "Answer": "marriage"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q198",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'parent'?",
    "Answer": "oya"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q199",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'speak'?",
    "Answer": "hanasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q200",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sukoshi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "a bit",
      "a little while"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q201",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shut'?",
    "Answer": "tojiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q202",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'time'?",
    "Answer": "toki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q203",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kome'?",
    "Answer": "rice (grain)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q204",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cut'?",
    "Answer": "kiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q205",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tanoshii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fun",
      "enjoyable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q206",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'clothes (colloquial)'?",
    "Answer": "fuku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q207",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'back'?",
    "Answer": "ushiro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q208",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'happy'?",
    "Answer": "ureshii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q209",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koshi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "waist",
      "lower back"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q210",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nichiyoubi'?",
    "Answer": "Sunday"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q211",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'daytime'?",
    "Answer": "hiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q212",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mother (colloquial)'?",
    "Answer": "okaasan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q213",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'university student'?",
    "Answer": "daigakusei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q214",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'end'?",
    "Answer": "owari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q215",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'se'?",
    "Answer": [
      "height",
      "stature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q216",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'help'?",
    "Answer": "tetsudau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q217",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'nose'?",
    "Answer": "hana"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q218",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "occur",
      "happen",
      "wake up",
      "get up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q219",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'place'?",
    "Answer": "noseru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q220",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanashii'?",
    "Answer": "sad"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q221",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shaberu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "chat",
      "talk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q222",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'in the near future'?",
    "Answer": "chikaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q223",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'amai'?",
    "Answer": "sweet"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q224",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'table'?",
    "Answer": "te-buru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q225",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tabemono'?",
    "Answer": "food (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q226",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hajimaru'?",
    "Answer": "begin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q227",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'game'?",
    "Answer": "ge-mu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q228",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ten'?",
    "Answer": "juu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q229",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'weather'?",
    "Answer": "tenki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q230",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atsui'?",
    "Answer": "hot (of weather)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q231",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'thick'?",
    "Answer": "futoi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q232",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ban'?",
    "Answer": [
      "evening",
      "night (from sunset to bedtime)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q233",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'doyoubi'?",
    "Answer": "Saturday"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q234",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sore",
      "painful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q235",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'otousan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "father",
      "dad (colloquial)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q236",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'probably'?",
    "Answer": "tabun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q237",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'clock'?",
    "Answer": "tokei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q238",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stay overnight'?",
    "Answer": "tomaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q239",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'how come'?",
    "Answer": "doushite"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q240",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kakeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hang",
      "put on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q241",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'magaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "make a turn",
      "turn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q242",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stomach'?",
    "Answer": "onaka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q243",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mi-tingu'?",
    "Answer": "meeting"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q244",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'dislike (habitual)'?",
    "Answer": "kirai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q245",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kinyoubi'?",
    "Answer": "Friday"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q246",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'need'?",
    "Answer": "iru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q247",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'to not be'?",
    "Answer": "nai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q248",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaze'?",
    "Answer": "cold (illness)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q249",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kiiroi'?",
    "Answer": "yellow"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q250",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yasashii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "gentle",
      "kind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q251",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hareru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be sunny",
      "clear up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q252",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'dirty'?",
    "Answer": "kitanai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q253",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chairo'?",
    "Answer": "brown"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q254",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be empty",
      "become less crowded"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q255",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'go up'?",
    "Answer": "noboru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q256",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'meal'?",
    "Answer": "gohan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q257",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'counter for days'?",
    "Answer": "nichi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q258",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaminoke'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hair",
      "each single hair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q259",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'switch on'?",
    "Answer": "tsukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q260",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'getsuyoubi'?",
    "Answer": "Monday"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q261",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hairu'?",
    "Answer": "enter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q262",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'katakana'?",
    "Answer": "katakana"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q263",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'this week'?",
    "Answer": "konshuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q264",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hiraku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "open (books",
      "eyes",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q265",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'water'?",
    "Answer": "mizu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q266",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'that (over there)'?",
    "Answer": "are"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q267",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ni'?",
    "Answer": "two"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q268",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shimeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tighten",
      "fasten"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q269",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bad (taste)'?",
    "Answer": "mazui"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q270",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hiragana'?",
    "Answer": "hiragana"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q271",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kumoru'?",
    "Answer": "become cloudy"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q272",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'touch'?",
    "Answer": "sawaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q273",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dame'?",
    "Answer": "no good"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q274",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nomimono'?",
    "Answer": [
      "beverage",
      "drink"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q275",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mokuyoubi'?",
    "Answer": "Thursday"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q276",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'day of the week'?",
    "Answer": "youbi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q277",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'soba'?",
    "Answer": [
      "side",
      "vicinity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q278",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kocchi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "here",
      "this way (casual)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q279",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kayoubi'?",
    "Answer": "Tuesday"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q280",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kawaku'?",
    "Answer": "be thirsty"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q281",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'san'?",
    "Answer": "three"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q282",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Wednesday'?",
    "Answer": "suiyoubi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q283",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'futatsu'?",
    "Answer": "two (things)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q284",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'this evening'?",
    "Answer": "konban"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q285",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sen'?",
    "Answer": "thousand"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q286",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'six days'?",
    "Answer": "muika"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q287",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'older sister'?",
    "Answer": "onesan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q288",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naoru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be repaired",
      "get fixed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q289",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'just a moment'?",
    "Answer": "chotto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q290",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'four (Japanese origin)'?",
    "Answer": "yon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q291",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'korekara'?",
    "Answer": [
      "from now on",
      "after this"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q292",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'think'?",
    "Answer": "kangaeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q293",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'modoru'?",
    "Answer": "return to a point of departure"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q294",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "change (something)",
      "alter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q295",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'morning'?",
    "Answer": "asa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q296",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tooth'?",
    "Answer": "ha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q297",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'work hard'?",
    "Answer": "ganbaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q298",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'keitaidenwa'?",
    "Answer": "cellular phone"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q299",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rain'?",
    "Answer": "ame"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q300",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'money (colloquial)'?",
    "Answer": "kane"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q301",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'easy'?",
    "Answer": "yasashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q302",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'older brother'?",
    "Answer": "oniisan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q303",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ooki'?",
    "Answer": "big"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q304",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chiisai'?",
    "Answer": "small"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q305",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'karai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "spicy",
      "hot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q306",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hachi'?",
    "Answer": "eight"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q307",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'over there'?",
    "Answer": "asoko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q308",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kuru'?",
    "Answer": "come"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q309",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mae'?",
    "Answer": [
      "front",
      "before"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q310",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'five days'?",
    "Answer": "itsuka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q311",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ippai'?",
    "Answer": "full"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q312",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sour'?",
    "Answer": "suppai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q313",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chigau'?",
    "Answer": [
      "differ",
      "be wrong"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q314",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'thin'?",
    "Answer": "hosoi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q315",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'three (things)'?",
    "Answer": "mittsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q316",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'youka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "eight days",
      "eighth of the month"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q317",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koukousei'?",
    "Answer": "high school student"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q318",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jouzu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "good",
      "skilled"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q319",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuyoi'?",
    "Answer": "strong"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q320",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nana'?",
    "Answer": "seven (Japanese origin)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q321",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hatsuka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "20 days",
      "20th of the month"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q322",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'left'?",
    "Answer": "hidari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q323",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'two days'?",
    "Answer": "futsuka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q324",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yottsu'?",
    "Answer": "four (things)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q325",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atatakai'?",
    "Answer": "warm"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q326",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'aru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "exist",
      "there is"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q327",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'good (informal/spoken form)'?",
    "Answer": "ii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q328",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ue'?",
    "Answer": [
      "up",
      "above"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q329",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'eki'?",
    "Answer": "train station"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q330",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tasty'?",
    "Answer": "oishii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q331",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kinou'?",
    "Answer": "yesterday (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q332",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kirei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pretty",
      "clean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q333",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'go'?",
    "Answer": "five"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q334",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'nine (things)'?",
    "Answer": "kokonotsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q335",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'favor'?",
    "Answer": "onegai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q336",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kotaeru'?",
    "Answer": "give an answer"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q337",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ahead'?",
    "Answer": "saki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q338",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'samui'?",
    "Answer": "cold (temperature of the air)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q339",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'four (Chinese origin)'?",
    "Answer": "shi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q340",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mikka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "three days",
      "third of the month"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q341",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'under'?",
    "Answer": "shita"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q342",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'all right'?",
    "Answer": "daijoubu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q343",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'otona'?",
    "Answer": "adult"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q344",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'take out'?",
    "Answer": "dasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q345",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(speakerâ€™s) father'?",
    "Answer": "chichi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q346",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(speakerâ€™s) mother'?",
    "Answer": "haha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q347",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'moon'?",
    "Answer": "tsuki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q348",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'younger sister'?",
    "Answer": "imouto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q349",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsumetai'?",
    "Answer": "cold (to touch)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q350",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'younger brother'?",
    "Answer": "otouto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q351",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'te'?",
    "Answer": "hand"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q352",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tooka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "ten days",
      "tenth of the month"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q353",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mouth'?",
    "Answer": "kuchi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q354",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'summer'?",
    "Answer": "natsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q355",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'seven (things)'?",
    "Answer": "nanatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q356",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sometimes'?",
    "Answer": "tokidoki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q357",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nani'?",
    "Answer": "what"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q358",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hito'?",
    "Answer": "person"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q359",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hitori'?",
    "Answer": "one person"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q360",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuitachi'?",
    "Answer": "first of the month"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q361",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'nine days'?",
    "Answer": "kokonoka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q362",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'direction'?",
    "Answer": "hou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q363",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'other (Japanese origin)'?",
    "Answer": "hoka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q364",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'I'?",
    "Answer": "boku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q365",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'want'?",
    "Answer": "hoshii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q366",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'man'?",
    "Answer": "ten thousand"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q367",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mieru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be visible",
      "can see"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q368",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'michi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "street",
      "way"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q369",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itsutsu'?",
    "Answer": "five (things)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q370",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'eye'?",
    "Answer": "me"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q371",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'eight (things)'?",
    "Answer": "yattsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q372",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stop (a carâ€¦). ___ (yameru) give up'?",
    "Answer": "tomeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q373",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yokka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "four days",
      "fourth of the month"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q374",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'night (from sunset to sunrise)'?",
    "Answer": "yoru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q375",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rainen'?",
    "Answer": "next year"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q376",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'roku'?",
    "Answer": "six"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q377",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bad'?",
    "Answer": "warui"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q378",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'otearai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "toilet",
      "bathroom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q379",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(someone elseâ€™s) husband'?",
    "Answer": "goshujin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q380",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hontouni'?",
    "Answer": [
      "really",
      "truly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q381",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'self'?",
    "Answer": "jibun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q382",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sake'?",
    "Answer": "tame"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q383",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be found'?",
    "Answer": "mitsukaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q384",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'take a rest'?",
    "Answer": "yasumu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q385",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'slowly'?",
    "Answer": "yukkuri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q386",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'muttsu'?",
    "Answer": "six (things)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q387",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hana'?",
    "Answer": "flower"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q388",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ugoku'?",
    "Answer": "move"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q389",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sen'?",
    "Answer": "line"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q390",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'seven days'?",
    "Answer": "nanoka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q391",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'except for'?",
    "Answer": "igai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q392",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'man'?",
    "Answer": "otoko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q393",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kare'?",
    "Answer": [
      "he",
      "oneâ€™s boyfriend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q394",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'onna'?",
    "Answer": "woman"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q395",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuma'?",
    "Answer": "woman"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q396",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hundred'?",
    "Answer": "hyaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q397",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'vicinity'?",
    "Answer": "atari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q398",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shop'?",
    "Answer": "mise"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q399",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be shut'?",
    "Answer": "shimaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q400",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mondai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "problem",
      "question"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q401",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hitsuyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "need",
      "necessary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q402",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'last long'?",
    "Answer": "motsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q403",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hiraku'?",
    "Answer": "open"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q404",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakunen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "last year (formal",
      "often used in writing)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q405",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be cured'?",
    "Answer": "naoru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q406",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'doru'?",
    "Answer": "dollar"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q407",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shisutemu'?",
    "Answer": "system (loan word)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q408",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ijou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "more than",
      "not less than"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q409",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'recent'?",
    "Answer": "saikin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q410",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sekai'?",
    "Answer": "world"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q411",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'konpyu-ta-'?",
    "Answer": "computer"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q412",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'give (to an inferior)'?",
    "Answer": "yaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q413",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'meaning'?",
    "Answer": "imi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q414",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'increase'?",
    "Answer": "fueru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q415",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'choose'?",
    "Answer": "erabu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q416",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seikatsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "life",
      "living"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q417",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'susumeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "go ahead",
      "proceed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q418",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'continue'?",
    "Answer": "tsuzukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q419",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hotondo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "almost",
      "hardly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q420",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaisha'?",
    "Answer": [
      "company",
      "corporation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q421",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'house'?",
    "Answer": "ie"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q422",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ooku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "much",
      "largely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q423",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hanashi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "talk",
      "story"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q424",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'go up'?",
    "Answer": "agaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q425",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'another'?",
    "Answer": "mou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q426",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atsumeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "collect",
      "gather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q427",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koe'?",
    "Answer": [
      "voice",
      "sound"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q428",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'for the first time'?",
    "Answer": "hajimete"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q429",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'change'?",
    "Answer": "kawaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q430",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mazu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "first of all",
      "to begin with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q431",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shakai'?",
    "Answer": "society"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q432",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'program booklet'?",
    "Answer": "puroguramu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q433",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chikara'?",
    "Answer": [
      "strength",
      "power"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q434",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'this time'?",
    "Answer": "konkai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q435",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'schedule'?",
    "Answer": "yotei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q436",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'as is'?",
    "Answer": "mama"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q437",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'television'?",
    "Answer": "terebi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q438",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'decrease'?",
    "Answer": "heru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q439",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kieru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be extinguished",
      "disappear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q440",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'family'?",
    "Answer": "kazoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q441",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kuraberu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "compare",
      "contrast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q442",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be born'?",
    "Answer": "umareru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q443",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'free'?",
    "Answer": "tada"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q444",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'korera'?",
    "Answer": "these"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q445",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiraberu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "investigate",
      "check"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q446",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'accident'?",
    "Answer": "jiko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q447",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'denwa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "telephone",
      "phone call"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q448",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'foreign country'?",
    "Answer": "gaikoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q449",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bank'?",
    "Answer": "ginkou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q450",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'juubun'?",
    "Answer": [
      "enough",
      "plentiful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q451",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'amari'?",
    "Answer": "(not) much"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q452",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'photograph'?",
    "Answer": "shashin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q453",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'repeat'?",
    "Answer": "kurikaesu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q454",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shurui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "kind",
      "type"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q455",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'opinion'?",
    "Answer": "iken"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q456",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'newspaper'?",
    "Answer": "shinbun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q457",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bunshou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sentence",
      "writing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q458",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'medatsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stand out",
      "be conspicuous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q459",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'opponent'?",
    "Answer": "aite"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q460",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'byouin'?",
    "Answer": "hospital"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q461",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atsui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "thick",
      "bulky"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q462",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'busy'?",
    "Answer": "isogashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q463",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'usui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "thin",
      "weak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q464",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kawa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "river",
      "stream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q465",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kurai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "dark",
      "gloomy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q466",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'class (in school)'?",
    "Answer": "kurasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q467",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kuroi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "black",
      "dark"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q468",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bus'?",
    "Answer": "basu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q469",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'blue'?",
    "Answer": "aoi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q470",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shopping'?",
    "Answer": "kaimono"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q471",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kusuri'?",
    "Answer": [
      "drug",
      "medicine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q472",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sugar'?",
    "Answer": "satou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q473",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yasumi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "holiday",
      "break"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q474",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'post office'?",
    "Answer": "yuubinkyoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q475",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'juusho'?",
    "Answer": "address"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q476",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kochira'?",
    "Answer": [
      "here",
      "this way (polite)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q477",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'purse'?",
    "Answer": "saifu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q478",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'passport'?",
    "Answer": "pasupo-to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q479",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'chair'?",
    "Answer": "isu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q480",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kawaii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "cute",
      "sweet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q481",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ojiisan'?",
    "Answer": "grandfather (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q482",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'postage stamp'?",
    "Answer": "kitte"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q483",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suzushii'?",
    "Answer": "cool (of temperature)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q484",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ikutsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "how many",
      "how old"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q485",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'menu'?",
    "Answer": "menyu-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q486",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'electricity'?",
    "Answer": "denki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q487",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'win'?",
    "Answer": "katsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q488",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'makeru'?",
    "Answer": "lose"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q489",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tateru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "build",
      "erect"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q490",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'diary'?",
    "Answer": "nikki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q491",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'urikire'?",
    "Answer": "sell out"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q492",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'omawarisan'?",
    "Answer": "police officer (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q493",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mezamashitokei'?",
    "Answer": "alarm clock"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q494",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'receipt (loan word)'?",
    "Answer": "reshi-to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q495",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tisshu'?",
    "Answer": "tissue"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q496",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'haburashi'?",
    "Answer": "toothbrush"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q497",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oriru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "go down",
      "come down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q498",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wash'?",
    "Answer": "arau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q499",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'part-time'?",
    "Answer": "pa-to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q500",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shimei'?",
    "Answer": "full name"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q501",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tonight'?",
    "Answer": "konya"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q502",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yonaka'?",
    "Answer": "midnight"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q503",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'raishuu'?",
    "Answer": "next week"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q504",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dareka'?",
    "Answer": "someone"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q505",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nan'?",
    "Answer": "what. ________. What is that?"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q506",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'this morning'?",
    "Answer": "kesa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q507",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sushi'?",
    "Answer": "sushi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q508",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'haku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "put on (shoes)",
      "wear (pants",
      "skirt)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q509",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'uncle'?",
    "Answer": "ojisan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q510",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'aunt'?",
    "Answer": "obasan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q511",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'obaasan'?",
    "Answer": "grandmother (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q512",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itoko'?",
    "Answer": "cousin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q513",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'dictionary (category)'?",
    "Answer": "jisho"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q514",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'breakfast'?",
    "Answer": "asagohan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q515",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'white'?",
    "Answer": "shiro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q516",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'which (casual)'?",
    "Answer": "docchi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q517",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'socchi'?",
    "Answer": "there (casual)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q518",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ashita'?",
    "Answer": "tomorrow (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q519",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'day after tomorrow (colloquial)'?",
    "Answer": "myougonichi/asatte"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q520",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ototoi'?",
    "Answer": "the day before yesterday (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q521",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'niwa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "garden",
      "yard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q522",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hidarigawa'?",
    "Answer": "left side"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q523",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'right side'?",
    "Answer": "migigawa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q524",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yubi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "finger",
      "toe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q525",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'glasses'?",
    "Answer": "megane"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q526",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bag'?",
    "Answer": "kaban"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q527",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'acchi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "other side",
      "over there (casual)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q528",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'otonashii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "gentle",
      "quiet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q529",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'not good at'?",
    "Answer": "heta"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q530",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'strict'?",
    "Answer": "kibishii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q531",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'by oneself'?",
    "Answer": "hitoride"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q532",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'answer'?",
    "Answer": "kotae"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q533",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'konogoro'?",
    "Answer": [
      "these days",
      "recently"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q534",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'regretful'?",
    "Answer": "zannen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q535",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shimau'?",
    "Answer": [
      "put away",
      "put in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q536",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'anxiety'?",
    "Answer": "shinpai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q537",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'outside'?",
    "Answer": "soto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q538",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taisetsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "important",
      "valuable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q539",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'just'?",
    "Answer": "choudo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q540",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'help'?",
    "Answer": "tasukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q541",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsutomeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "serve",
      "hold a job"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q542",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'take along'?",
    "Answer": "tsureteiku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q543",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'joubu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "healthy",
      "sturdy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q544",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nigiyaka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "lively",
      "exciting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q545",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sleepy'?",
    "Answer": "nemui"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q546",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yama'?",
    "Answer": "mountain"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q547",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bridge'?",
    "Answer": "hashi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q548",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'come to a stop'?",
    "Answer": "tomaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q549",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'furu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fall",
      "come down (rain",
      "snow",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q550",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hontou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "reality",
      "genuine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q551",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'town'?",
    "Answer": "machi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q552",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sweets'?",
    "Answer": "okashi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q553",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yurui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "slack",
      "loose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q554",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yoi'?",
    "Answer": "good (formal/written form)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q555",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'welcome (greeting)'?",
    "Answer": "youkoso"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q556",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'omiyage'?",
    "Answer": "souvenir (polite)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q557",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ryoushin'?",
    "Answer": "parents"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q558",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'waiter'?",
    "Answer": "we-ta-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q559",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'waitress'?",
    "Answer": "we-toresu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q560",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zettaini'?",
    "Answer": [
      "absolutely",
      "definitely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q561",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'feast'?",
    "Answer": "gochisou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q562",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fork'?",
    "Answer": "fo-ku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q563",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'supu-n'?",
    "Answer": "spoon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q564",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bin'?",
    "Answer": "bottle"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q565",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be on'?",
    "Answer": "tsuku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q566",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'soy sauce'?",
    "Answer": "shouyu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q567",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rice bowl'?",
    "Answer": "chawan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q568",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kimeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "decide",
      "agree upon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q569",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanjiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "feel",
      "sense"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q570",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ikiru'?",
    "Answer": "live (oneâ€™s life)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q571",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'move (something)'?",
    "Answer": "ugokasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q572",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'break'?",
    "Answer": "kowareru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q573",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'review'?",
    "Answer": "fukushuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q574",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'eyebrow'?",
    "Answer": "mayu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q575",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'visitor'?",
    "Answer": "kyaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q576",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsukue'?",
    "Answer": "desk"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q577",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'furo'?",
    "Answer": "bath"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q578",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hot water'?",
    "Answer": "yu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q579",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nurui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tepid",
      "lukewarm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q580",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cold medicine'?",
    "Answer": "kazegusuri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q581",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kutsushita'?",
    "Answer": "socks"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q582",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tobacco'?",
    "Answer": "tabako"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q583",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'iced coffee'?",
    "Answer": "aisuko-hi-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q584",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tempura'?",
    "Answer": "Japanese deep-fried food"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q585",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'flesh'?",
    "Answer": "niku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q586",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakuya'?",
    "Answer": [
      "last night",
      "last evening (colloquial)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q587",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be in fashion'?",
    "Answer": "hayaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q588",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bring (a person)'?",
    "Answer": "tsuretekuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q589",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kata'?",
    "Answer": "person (polite form)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q590",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'zero'?",
    "Answer": "rei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q591",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kumo'?",
    "Answer": "cloud"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q592",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sky'?",
    "Answer": "sora"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q593",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ninki'?",
    "Answer": "popularity"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q594",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(oneâ€™s own) older brother (polite)'?",
    "Answer": "niisan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q595",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'neesan'?",
    "Answer": "(oneâ€™s own) older sister (polite)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q596",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Heisei era'?",
    "Answer": "heisei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q597",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maitsuki'?",
    "Answer": "every month"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q598",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'half a day'?",
    "Answer": "hannichi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q599",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hantsuki'?",
    "Answer": "half a month"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q600",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naruhodo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "I see",
      "really"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q601",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'in short'?",
    "Answer": "tsumari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q602",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sonomama'?",
    "Answer": [
      "as it is",
      "just like that"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q603",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'clearly'?",
    "Answer": "hakkiri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q604",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taihen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "awful",
      "hard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q605",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kantan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "simple",
      "easy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q606",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'look like'?",
    "Answer": "niteiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q607",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'odoroku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be surprised",
      "be startled"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q608",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iya/ kira-i'?",
    "Answer": "dislike (situational)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q609",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fight'?",
    "Answer": "kenka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q610",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be late'?",
    "Answer": "okureru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q611",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ninjin'?",
    "Answer": "carrot"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q612",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jagaimo'?",
    "Answer": "potato"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q613",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'eggplant'?",
    "Answer": "nasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q614",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'kettle'?",
    "Answer": "yakan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q615",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hanashiau'?",
    "Answer": [
      "discuss",
      "talk over"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q616",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'leave'?",
    "Answer": "nokosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q617",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gochisousuru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "treat",
      "host (a meal)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q618",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fit'?",
    "Answer": "au"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q619",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(go straight and) hit'?",
    "Answer": "ataru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q620",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atsumaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "gather",
      "be collected"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q621",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'place'?",
    "Answer": "basho"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q622",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sea'?",
    "Answer": "umi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q623",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'boy (between 7 and 18 years old)'?",
    "Answer": "shounen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q624",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'grandchild'?",
    "Answer": "mago"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q625",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seito'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pupil",
      "student"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q626",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koukou'?",
    "Answer": "high school (for short)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q627",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'older'?",
    "Answer": "toshiue"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q628",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sotsugyou'?",
    "Answer": "graduation"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q629",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'movement'?",
    "Answer": "undou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q630",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'senshu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "athlete",
      "(sports) player"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q631",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'movie'?",
    "Answer": "eiga"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q632",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'English'?",
    "Answer": "eigo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q633",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tegami'?",
    "Answer": "letter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q634",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'animal'?",
    "Answer": "doubutsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q635",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sound'?",
    "Answer": "oto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q636",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaigai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "overseas",
      "abroad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q637",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'foreigner'?",
    "Answer": "gaikokujin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q638",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kikoku'?",
    "Answer": "return to oneâ€™s country"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q639",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'karera'?",
    "Answer": "they"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q640",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'machine'?",
    "Answer": "kikai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q641",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kihon'?",
    "Answer": "basics"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q642",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'this time'?",
    "Answer": "kondo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q643",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'saigo'?",
    "Answer": "last"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q644",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'saisho'?",
    "Answer": [
      "first",
      "outset"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q645",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'preparation'?",
    "Answer": "junbi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q646",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'advance'?",
    "Answer": "susumu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q647",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chokusetsu'?",
    "Answer": "directly"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q648",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'specially'?",
    "Answer": "tokuni"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q649",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'reach'?",
    "Answer": "todoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q650",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'why'?",
    "Answer": "naze"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q651",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'line up'?",
    "Answer": "narabu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q652",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'carry'?",
    "Answer": "hakobu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q653",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naosu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "repair",
      "fix"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q654",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hantai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "oppose",
      "object"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q655",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'baai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "situation",
      "case"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q656",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'detailed'?",
    "Answer": "kuwashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q657",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itazura'?",
    "Answer": [
      "mischief",
      "prank"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q658",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'celebrate'?",
    "Answer": "oiwai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q659",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'comb'?",
    "Answer": "kushi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q660",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koboreru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "spill",
      "overflow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q661",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'convey'?",
    "Answer": "tsutaeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q662",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'knee'?",
    "Answer": "hiza"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q663",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hiji'?",
    "Answer": "elbow"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q664",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'makura'?",
    "Answer": "pillow"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q665",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tatemono'?",
    "Answer": [
      "building",
      "structure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q666",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'douro'?",
    "Answer": "road"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q667",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'intersection'?",
    "Answer": "yotsukado"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q668",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'corner (to turn)'?",
    "Answer": "magarikado"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q669",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'keisatsu'?",
    "Answer": "police"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q670",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'air'?",
    "Answer": "kuuki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q671",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sport'?",
    "Answer": "supo-tsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q672",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'chance'?",
    "Answer": "chansu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q673",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'dry cleaning'?",
    "Answer": "kuri-ningu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q674",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sa-bisu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "service",
      "on the house"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q675",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'guru-pu'?",
    "Answer": "group"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q676",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'oneâ€™s house'?",
    "Answer": "jitaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q677",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'home'?",
    "Answer": "katei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q678",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'term'?",
    "Answer": "kikan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q679",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'year'?",
    "Answer": "nendo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q680",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'keiken'?",
    "Answer": [
      "experience",
      "knowledge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q681",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'anzen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "safety",
      "security"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q682",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'danger'?",
    "Answer": "kiken"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q683",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'attention'?",
    "Answer": "chuui"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q684",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'success'?",
    "Answer": "seikou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q685",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'endeavor'?",
    "Answer": "doryoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q686",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'explanation'?",
    "Answer": "setsumei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q687",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'earthquake'?",
    "Answer": "jishin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q688",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'surgical operation'?",
    "Answer": "shujutsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q689",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'burn'?",
    "Answer": "yakedo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q690",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kadai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "task",
      "assignment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q691",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ko'?",
    "Answer": [
      "young child",
      "kid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q692",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kakunin'?",
    "Answer": "confirmation"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q693",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jissai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "reality",
      "actual state"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q694",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kokusai'?",
    "Answer": "international (used in compound nouns)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q695",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaigi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "conference",
      "meeting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q696",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'teian'?",
    "Answer": [
      "proposition",
      "proposal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q697",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'office'?",
    "Answer": "jimusho"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q698",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyouju'?",
    "Answer": "professor"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q699",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seiki'?",
    "Answer": "century"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q700",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'all over'?",
    "Answer": "achikochi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q701",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'there'?",
    "Answer": "sochira"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q702",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'over there'?",
    "Answer": "achira"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q703",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'if'?",
    "Answer": "moshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q704",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'urusai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "noisy",
      "annoying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q705",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stiff'?",
    "Answer": "katai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q706",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fukai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "deep",
      "profound"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q707",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'omoshiroi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "interesting",
      "amusing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q708",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'entirely'?",
    "Answer": "mattaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q709",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'half'?",
    "Answer": "hanbun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q710",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'normal'?",
    "Answer": "futsuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q711",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'amount'?",
    "Answer": "bun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q712",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bunka'?",
    "Answer": "culture"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q713",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mainichi'?",
    "Answer": "every day"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q714",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kiwotsukeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be careful about",
      "pay attention to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q715",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'protect'?",
    "Answer": "mamoru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q716",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'of course'?",
    "Answer": "mochiron"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q717",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'as expected'?",
    "Answer": "yahari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q718",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ikura'?",
    "Answer": "how much (money)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q719",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yoroshiku'?",
    "Answer": "oneâ€™s regards"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q720",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'who (polite)'?",
    "Answer": "donata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q721",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yurusu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "permit",
      "forgive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q722",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wakeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "divide",
      "share"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q723",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shizen'?",
    "Answer": "nature"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q724",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'apartment'?",
    "Answer": "apa-to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q725",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hoteru'?",
    "Answer": "hotel"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q726",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'personal computer'?",
    "Answer": "pasokon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q727",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'good at'?",
    "Answer": "umai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q728",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'akarui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bright",
      "cheerful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q729",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'isogu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hurry",
      "do quickly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q730",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'uta'?",
    "Answer": "song"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q731",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chuugakkou'?",
    "Answer": "junior high school"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q732",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'test'?",
    "Answer": "tesuto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q733",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'posuto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "postbox",
      "mailbox"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q734",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hankachi'?",
    "Answer": "handkerchief"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q735",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hair'?",
    "Answer": "kami"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q736",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'boushi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hat",
      "cap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q737",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaburu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "wear",
      "put on (on oneâ€™s head)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q738",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'burausu'?",
    "Answer": "blouse"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q739",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shuumatsu'?",
    "Answer": "weekend"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q740",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'senshuu'?",
    "Answer": "last week"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q741",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'saraishuu'?",
    "Answer": "the week after next"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q742",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itsuka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "some time",
      "some day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q743",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shukudai'?",
    "Answer": "homework"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q744",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'key'?",
    "Answer": "kagi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q745",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'umbrella'?",
    "Answer": "kasa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q746",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'norikaeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "change",
      "transfer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q747",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'face'?",
    "Answer": "mukau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q748",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bookstore (colloquial)'?",
    "Answer": "honya"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q749",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tea (polite)'?",
    "Answer": "ocha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q750",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaisatsuguchi'?",
    "Answer": "ticket gate"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q751",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hare'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fine weather",
      "clear sky"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q752",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bus stop'?",
    "Answer": "basutei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q753",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cloudy weather'?",
    "Answer": "kumori"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q754",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shio'?",
    "Answer": "salt"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q755",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'a lot'?",
    "Answer": "takusan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q756",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hate'?",
    "Answer": "daikirai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q757",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "inside",
      "middle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q758",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nikai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "second floor",
      "upstairs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q759",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nakusu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "lose",
      "get rid of"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q760",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maamaa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "OK",
      "not bad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q761",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kiiro'?",
    "Answer": "yellow color"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q762",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lunch (loan word)'?",
    "Answer": "ranchi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q763",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakana'?",
    "Answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q764",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'taste'?",
    "Answer": "aji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q765",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ringo'?",
    "Answer": "apple"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q766",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mikan'?",
    "Answer": "tangerine"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q767",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'plate'?",
    "Answer": "sara"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q768",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'coffee'?",
    "Answer": "ko-hi-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q769",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cup'?",
    "Answer": "koppu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q770",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'two persons'?",
    "Answer": "futari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q771",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yamu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stop",
      "cease"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q772",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'nine'?",
    "Answer": "kyuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q773",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hiruma'?",
    "Answer": [
      "daytime",
      "during the day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q774",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'about when'?",
    "Answer": "itsugoro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q775",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ji'?",
    "Answer": [
      "(individual) character",
      "letter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q776",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'seven (Chinese origin)'?",
    "Answer": "nana"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q777",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'change (of money)'?",
    "Answer": "otsuri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q778",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'surname'?",
    "Answer": "myouji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q779",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(oneâ€™s own) uncle'?",
    "Answer": "oji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q780",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(oneâ€™s own) aunt'?",
    "Answer": "oba"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q781",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sofu'?",
    "Answer": "grandfather (formal)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q782",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sobo'?",
    "Answer": "grandmother (formal)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q783",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'importance'?",
    "Answer": "daiji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q784",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'view'?",
    "Answer": "mikata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q785",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tori'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bird",
      "poultry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q786",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'dog'?",
    "Answer": "inu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q787",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'henji'?",
    "Answer": [
      "reply",
      "answer",
      "response"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q788",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'again'?",
    "Answer": "mata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q789",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nenkan'?",
    "Answer": "period of one year"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q790",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ao'?",
    "Answer": [
      "blue",
      "green"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q791",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'red color'?",
    "Answer": "aka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q792",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shingou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "signal",
      "traffic light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q793",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'en'?",
    "Answer": "circle"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q794",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hijouni'?",
    "Answer": [
      "very",
      "extremely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q795",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'complicated'?",
    "Answer": "fukuzatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q796",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'peace'?",
    "Answer": "heiwa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q797",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mawaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "turn round",
      "go around"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q798",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'young person'?",
    "Answer": "wakamono"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q799",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'snow'?",
    "Answer": "yuki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q800",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'umai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sweet",
      "delicious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q801",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'omoidasu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "recollect",
      "recall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q802",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kikoeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hear",
      "be heard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q803",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'borrow'?",
    "Answer": "kariru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q804",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'return'?",
    "Answer": "kaesu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q805",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'uketoru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "receive",
      "get"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q806",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suteru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "discard",
      "abandon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q807",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'together'?",
    "Answer": "issho"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q808",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'play'?",
    "Answer": "asobi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q809",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'move'?",
    "Answer": "utsusu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q810",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ookisa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "size",
      "dimension"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q811",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'thought'?",
    "Answer": "kangae"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q812",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kuukou'?",
    "Answer": "airport (for public transportation)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q813",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shuppatsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "departure",
      "starting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q814",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'map'?",
    "Answer": "chizu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q815",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'unten'?",
    "Answer": "drive"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q816",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get off'?",
    "Answer": "oriru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q817",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gasu'?",
    "Answer": "gas (loan word)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q818",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'without exception'?",
    "Answer": "kanarazu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q819",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'camera'?",
    "Answer": "kamera"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q820",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kayou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "go to and from",
      "frequent a place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q821",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'suddenly'?",
    "Answer": "kyuuni"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q822",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'office worker'?",
    "Answer": "sarari-man"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q823",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'salary'?",
    "Answer": "kyuuryou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q824",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyoku'?",
    "Answer": "piece of music"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q825",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cut well'?",
    "Answer": "kireru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q826",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tadashii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "correct",
      "righteous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q827",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kurushii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "painful",
      "agonizing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q828",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'minute'?",
    "Answer": "komakai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q829",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shizuka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "quiet",
      "tranquil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q830",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kenkou'?",
    "Answer": "health"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q831",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gorufu'?",
    "Answer": "golf"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q832",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'course'?",
    "Answer": "ko-su"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q833",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tanomu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "order",
      "ask for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q834",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be in trouble'?",
    "Answer": "komaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q835",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'all the time'?",
    "Answer": "zutto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q836",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tatoeba'?",
    "Answer": "for example"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q837",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsumori'?",
    "Answer": [
      "intention",
      "purpose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q838",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'a little while'?",
    "Answer": "shibaraku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q839",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'introduction'?",
    "Answer": "shoukai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q840",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'elementary school'?",
    "Answer": "shougakkou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q841",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'park'?",
    "Answer": "kouen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q842",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chuugaku'?",
    "Answer": "junior high"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q843",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'results'?",
    "Answer": "seiseki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q844",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'textbook'?",
    "Answer": "kyoukasho"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q845",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "seat",
      "oneâ€™s place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q846",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyoushitsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "classroom",
      "class"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q847",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyoushi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "teacher",
      "instructor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q848",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'exam'?",
    "Answer": "shiken"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q849",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'goukaku'?",
    "Answer": "pass an examination"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q850",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suugaku'?",
    "Answer": "mathematics"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q851",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'numeric characters'?",
    "Answer": "suuji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q852",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ongaku'?",
    "Answer": "music"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q853",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shokuji'?",
    "Answer": "meal"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q854",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kabe'?",
    "Answer": [
      "wall",
      "partition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q855",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'believe'?",
    "Answer": "shinjiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q856",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sodateru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bring up",
      "raise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q857",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fall over'?",
    "Answer": "taoreru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q858",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'drop'?",
    "Answer": "otosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q859",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'substitute'?",
    "Answer": "kawaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q860",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'takushi-'?",
    "Answer": "taxi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q861",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tashika'?",
    "Answer": [
      "for sure",
      "for certain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q862",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tateru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stand",
      "set up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q863",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'junior high school student'?",
    "Answer": "chuugakusei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q864",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sell'?",
    "Answer": "ureru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q865",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "arrive at",
      "reach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q866",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kimaru'?",
    "Answer": "be decided"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q867",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kazaru'?",
    "Answer": "decorate"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q868",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'kill'?",
    "Answer": "korosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q869",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lower'?",
    "Answer": "sageru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q870",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okuru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "offer",
      "give"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q871",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tazuneru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "visit",
      "go to see"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q872",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'utsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hit",
      "strike"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q873",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'soudan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "consultation",
      "advice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q874",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'entrance'?",
    "Answer": "genkan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q875",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyoudai'?",
    "Answer": "sibling"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q876",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'eldest son'?",
    "Answer": "chounan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q877",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'height'?",
    "Answer": "takasa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q878",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'you'?",
    "Answer": "things to do"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q879",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'age'?",
    "Answer": "jidai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q880",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'position'?",
    "Answer": "ichi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q881",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'season'?",
    "Answer": "kisetsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q882",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ana'?",
    "Answer": "hole"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q883",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ura'?",
    "Answer": [
      "the back",
      "the reverse side"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q884",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'island (Japanese origin)'?",
    "Answer": "shima"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q885",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaigan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "seashore",
      "coast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q886",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'garasu'?",
    "Answer": "glass (material)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q887",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'natural'?",
    "Answer": "shizen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q888",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaze'?",
    "Answer": "wind"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q889",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'science'?",
    "Answer": "kagaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q890",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sun'?",
    "Answer": "taiyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q891",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taifuu'?",
    "Answer": "typhoon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q892",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'north'?",
    "Answer": "kita"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q893",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'uma'?",
    "Answer": "horse"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q894",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gyuuniku'?",
    "Answer": "beef"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q895",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zasshi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "magazine",
      "journal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q896",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'novel'?",
    "Answer": "shousetsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q897",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taishikan'?",
    "Answer": "embassy"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q898",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'malfunction'?",
    "Answer": "koshou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q899",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'temperature'?",
    "Answer": "ondo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q900",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nanika'?",
    "Answer": [
      "something",
      "some"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q901",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mukou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "over there",
      "on the other side"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q902",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mannaka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "center",
      "middle (casual)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q903",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tooku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "far away",
      "at a distance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q904",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'side'?",
    "Answer": "yoko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q905",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsumaranai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "boring",
      "dull"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q906",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'excellent'?",
    "Answer": "subarashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q907",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maitoshi/ mainen'?",
    "Answer": "every year (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q908",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'raigetsu'?",
    "Answer": "next month"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q909",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'date and time'?",
    "Answer": "nichiji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q910",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yuugata'?",
    "Answer": [
      "early evening",
      "at dusk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q911",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pass'?",
    "Answer": "tooru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q912",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jidousha'?",
    "Answer": "automobile"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q913",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nareru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "grow accustomed to",
      "get used to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q914",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'take (a photograph)'?",
    "Answer": "toru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q915",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yatto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "at last",
      "finally"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q916",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'knock'?",
    "Answer": "dondon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q917",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naraberu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "line up",
      "arrange"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q918",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nigeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "escape",
      "run away"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q919",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hand over'?",
    "Answer": "watasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q920",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'price'?",
    "Answer": "nedan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q921",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ryouhou'?",
    "Answer": "both"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q922",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yakusoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "promise",
      "vow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q923",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ichibu'?",
    "Answer": "part"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q924",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rajio'?",
    "Answer": "radio"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q925",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be hospitalized'?",
    "Answer": "nyuuin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q926",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'news'?",
    "Answer": "nyu-su"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q927",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'travel'?",
    "Answer": "ryokou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q928",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'youi'?",
    "Answer": "preparation"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q929",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nobiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stretch",
      "grow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q930",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'party'?",
    "Answer": "pa-ti-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q931",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'beer'?",
    "Answer": "bi-ru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q932",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hayaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "early",
      "soon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q933",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bangumi'?",
    "Answer": "program"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q934",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bideo'?",
    "Answer": "video"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q935",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'increase'?",
    "Answer": "fuyasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q936",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wave'?",
    "Answer": "furu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q937",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'welcome'?",
    "Answer": "mukaeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q938",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'unreasonable'?",
    "Answer": "muri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q939",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rare'?",
    "Answer": "mezurashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q940",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yuumei'?",
    "Answer": "famous"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q941",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be happy'?",
    "Answer": "yorokobu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q942",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ryuugaku'?",
    "Answer": "study abroad"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q943",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ryouri'?",
    "Answer": "cooking"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q944",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'vegetable'?",
    "Answer": "yasai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q945",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wakareru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be divided",
      "split off"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q946",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'special'?",
    "Answer": "tokubetsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q947",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'reason'?",
    "Answer": "riyuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q948",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'freedom'?",
    "Answer": "jiyuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q949",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'direction'?",
    "Answer": "houkou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q950",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nokoru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "remain",
      "be left over"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q951",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'building'?",
    "Answer": "biru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q952",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'matomeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "gather together",
      "put in order"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q953",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nagareru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "flow",
      "run"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q954",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sweater'?",
    "Answer": "se-ta-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q955",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shirt'?",
    "Answer": "shatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q956",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'laundry'?",
    "Answer": "sentaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q957",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'make a mistake'?",
    "Answer": "machigaeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q958",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ice cream'?",
    "Answer": "aisukuri-mu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q959",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kawaku'?",
    "Answer": "become dry"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q960",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sameru'?",
    "Answer": "cool off"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q961",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iroiro'?",
    "Answer": "a variety of"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q962",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'motteiku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "take",
      "bring"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q963",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'change clothes'?",
    "Answer": "kigaeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q964",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sekken'?",
    "Answer": "soap"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q965",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yakyuu'?",
    "Answer": "baseball"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q966",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chyuushoku'?",
    "Answer": "lunch"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q967",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'choushoku'?",
    "Answer": "breakfast"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q968",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nemuru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sleep",
      "lie idle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q969",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hajime'?",
    "Answer": "beginning"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q970",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fire",
      "flame"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q971",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'west'?",
    "Answer": "nishi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q972",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'higashi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "east",
      "eastern"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q973",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'minami'?",
    "Answer": "south"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q974",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'supper'?",
    "Answer": "yuushoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q975",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nakanaka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "rather",
      "pretty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q976",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'encourage'?",
    "Answer": "hagemasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q977",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tear'?",
    "Answer": "namida"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q978",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yume'?",
    "Answer": "dream"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q979",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shokuba'?",
    "Answer": [
      "place of work",
      "office"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q980",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'next to'?",
    "Answer": "tonari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q981",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'apartment'?",
    "Answer": "manshon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q982",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'erebe-ta-'?",
    "Answer": "elevator"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q983",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mado'?",
    "Answer": "window"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q984",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'osu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "push",
      "press down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q985",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nyuugaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "enter a school",
      "matriculate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q986",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'door'?",
    "Answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q987",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toori'?",
    "Answer": [
      "street",
      "road"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q988",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'die'?",
    "Answer": "nakunaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q989",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fuufu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "husband and wife",
      "married couple"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q990",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'josei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "woman",
      "female (formal)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q991",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mori'?",
    "Answer": "forest"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q992",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'torakku'?",
    "Answer": "truck"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q993",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'reko-do'?",
    "Answer": "record"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q994",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'netsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "heat",
      "fever"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q995",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pe-ji'?",
    "Answer": "page"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q996",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'odoru'?",
    "Answer": "dance"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q997",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'length'?",
    "Answer": "nagasa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q998",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atsusa'?",
    "Answer": "thickness"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q999",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'himitsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "secret",
      "privacy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1000",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'great'?",
    "Answer": "sugoi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1001",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'kind'?",
    "Answer": "shinsetsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1002",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'absolutely'?",
    "Answer": "zettai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1003",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sengetsu'?",
    "Answer": "last month"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1004",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the year before last (colloquial)'?",
    "Answer": "ototoshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1005",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fuyuyasumi'?",
    "Answer": "winter vacation"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1006",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'summer vacation'?",
    "Answer": "natsuyasumi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1007",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'day off'?",
    "Answer": "kyuujitsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1008",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shougatsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "New Year",
      "January"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1009",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'memory'?",
    "Answer": "omoide"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1010",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'occasionally'?",
    "Answer": "tamani"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1011",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okashii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "strange",
      "peculiar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1012",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'asai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "shallow",
      "superficial"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1013",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'you (referring to fellows or subordinates)'?",
    "Answer": "kimi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1014",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okusan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "(somone elseâ€™s) wife",
      "married woman"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1015",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'akachan'?",
    "Answer": "baby (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1016",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shougakusei'?",
    "Answer": "elementary school student"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1017",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kasu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "lend",
      "lease"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1018",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kazoeru'?",
    "Answer": "count"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1019",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'give birth'?",
    "Answer": "umu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1020",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be brought up'?",
    "Answer": "sodatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1021",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zehi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "by all means",
      "please"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1022",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kuro'?",
    "Answer": "black"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1023",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'toy'?",
    "Answer": "omocha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1024",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kutsu'?",
    "Answer": "shoes"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1025",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'contact'?",
    "Answer": "renraku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1026",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'message'?",
    "Answer": "dengon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1027",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'deposit'?",
    "Answer": "azukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1028",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sagaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "go down",
      "drop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1029",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'swim'?",
    "Answer": "oyogu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1030",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'part-time job'?",
    "Answer": "arubaito"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1031",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'coat'?",
    "Answer": "ko-to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1032",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hobby'?",
    "Answer": "shumi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1033",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'walk'?",
    "Answer": "sanpo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1034",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiawase'?",
    "Answer": [
      "happiness",
      "satisfied (colloquial)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1035",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'anshin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "peace of mind",
      "relief"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1036",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oozei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "large numbers",
      "a lot of (people)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1037",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'isha'?",
    "Answer": [
      "doctor (colloquial",
      "plain)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1038",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'driver'?",
    "Answer": "untenshu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1039",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bullet train'?",
    "Answer": "shinkansen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1040",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oufuku'?",
    "Answer": "round trip"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1041",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kopi-'?",
    "Answer": [
      "copy",
      "photocopy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1042",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "inner part",
      "the back"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1043",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'weight'?",
    "Answer": "omosa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1044",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'intimate'?",
    "Answer": "shitashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1045",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'repair'?",
    "Answer": "shuuri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1046",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'card'?",
    "Answer": "ka-do"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1047",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'greet'?",
    "Answer": "aisatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1048",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaidan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "steps",
      "flight of stairs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1049",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hand out'?",
    "Answer": "kubaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1050",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kotowaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "refuse",
      "turn down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1051",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'gram'?",
    "Answer": "guramu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1052",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "strong",
      "concentrated"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1053",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kowasu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "break (something)",
      "destroy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1054",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakura'?",
    "Answer": [
      "cherry tree",
      "cherry blossom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1055",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'way'?",
    "Answer": "shikata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1056",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'e'?",
    "Answer": [
      "picture",
      "painting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1057",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kion'?",
    "Answer": "air temperature"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1058",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shinamono'?",
    "Answer": [
      "article",
      "goods"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1059",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "inhale",
      "suck"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1060",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'annai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "guide",
      "guidance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1061",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suki-'?",
    "Answer": [
      "ski",
      "skiing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1062",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wealthy person'?",
    "Answer": "kanemochi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1063",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tazuneru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "inquire",
      "ask"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1064",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tataku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tap",
      "hit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1065",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaeri'?",
    "Answer": [
      "return",
      "going home"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1066",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tamago'?",
    "Answer": "egg"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1067",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koori'?",
    "Answer": "ice"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1068",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'student studying abroad'?",
    "Answer": "ryuugakusei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1069",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'software'?",
    "Answer": "sofuto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1070",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'haisha'?",
    "Answer": "dentist"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1071",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'keru'?",
    "Answer": "kick"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1072",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "lay",
      "spread"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1073",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'some moments'?",
    "Answer": "hitotoki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1074",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koutsuujiko'?",
    "Answer": "traffic accident"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1075",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'meet'?",
    "Answer": "au"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1076",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'invitation'?",
    "Answer": "shoutai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1077",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'saku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bloom",
      "blossom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1078",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '20 years old'?",
    "Answer": "hatachi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1079",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'silver'?",
    "Answer": "gin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1080",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'inside'?",
    "Answer": "uchigawa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1081",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ike'?",
    "Answer": "pond"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1082",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ishi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stone",
      "small rock"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1083",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'love'?",
    "Answer": "ai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1084",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'section'?",
    "Answer": "ka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1085",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'daigakuin'?",
    "Answer": "graduate school"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1086",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'daidokoro'?",
    "Answer": "kitchen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1087",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'color (loan word)'?",
    "Answer": "kara-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1088",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pickpocket'?",
    "Answer": "suri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1089",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'camping'?",
    "Answer": "kyanpu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1090",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'motorbike'?",
    "Answer": "o-tobai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1091",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tatsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be built",
      "be erected"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1092",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sting'?",
    "Answer": "sasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1093",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iikata'?",
    "Answer": [
      "way of speaking",
      "expression"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1094",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sink'?",
    "Answer": "shizumu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1095",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'set up'?",
    "Answer": "kumitateru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1096",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'terrible'?",
    "Answer": "osoroshii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1097",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'foreigner'?",
    "Answer": "gaijin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1098",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ushi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "cattle",
      "cow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1099",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cafeteria'?",
    "Answer": "shokudou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1100",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mainen'?",
    "Answer": "every year (formal)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1101",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maishuu'?",
    "Answer": "every week"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1102",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'how many times'?",
    "Answer": "nando"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1103",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nakanaka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "not easily",
      "not readily"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1104",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "earlier",
      "only a moment ago"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1105",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hisashiburi'?",
    "Answer": "after a long time"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1106",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'benri'?",
    "Answer": "convenience"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1107",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'meiwaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "trouble",
      "annoyance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1108",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'so much'?",
    "Answer": "sonnani"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1109",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be surprised'?",
    "Answer": "bikkurisuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1110",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tariru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "suffice",
      "be enough"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1111",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get tired'?",
    "Answer": "tsukareru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1112",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cruel'?",
    "Answer": "hidoi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1113",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zenzen'?",
    "Answer": "(not ) at all"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1114",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cat'?",
    "Answer": "neko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1115",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'depa-to'?",
    "Answer": "department store (loan word)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1116",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toire'?",
    "Answer": "toilet"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1117",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chikatetsu'?",
    "Answer": "subway"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1118",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chuushajou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "parking area",
      "parking lot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1119",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'butsukaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hit",
      "bump into"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1120",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(passenger) fare'?",
    "Answer": "unchin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1121",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'commuting to school'?",
    "Answer": "tsuugaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1122",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'miokuru'?",
    "Answer": "see (someone) off"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1123",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "cry",
      "weep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1124",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'restaurant'?",
    "Answer": "resutoran"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1125",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'memo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "memo",
      "note"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1126",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yoyaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "reservation",
      "appointment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1127",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bangou'?",
    "Answer": "assigned number"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1128",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chuumon'?",
    "Answer": "order"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1129",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pan'?",
    "Answer": "bread"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1130",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wain'?",
    "Answer": "wine"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1131",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zairyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "material",
      "ingredient"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1132",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pork'?",
    "Answer": "butaniku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1133",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bake'?",
    "Answer": "yaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1134",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(pleasant) smell'?",
    "Answer": "nioi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1135",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'attach'?",
    "Answer": "tsukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1136",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lose weight'?",
    "Answer": "yaseru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1137",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'todokeru'?",
    "Answer": "deliver"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1138",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be in time'?",
    "Answer": "maniau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1139",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'turn'?",
    "Answer": "muku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1140",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuyosa'?",
    "Answer": "strength"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1141",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tokui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "oneâ€™s specialty",
      "be good at"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1142",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'spread on'?",
    "Answer": "nuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1143",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'throw'?",
    "Answer": "nageru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1144",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'narau'?",
    "Answer": [
      "learn",
      "take lessons"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1145",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chuumoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "attention",
      "notice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1146",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'future'?",
    "Answer": "mirai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1147",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hako'?",
    "Answer": [
      "box",
      "case"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1148",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'right hand'?",
    "Answer": "migite"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1149",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hidarite'?",
    "Answer": "left hand"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1150",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pool'?",
    "Answer": "pu-ru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1151",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'piano'?",
    "Answer": "piano"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1152",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shine'?",
    "Answer": "hikaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1153",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fumu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "step on",
      "tread on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1154",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'betsubetsu'?",
    "Answer": "separately"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1155",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ball'?",
    "Answer": "bo-ru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1156",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'grasp'?",
    "Answer": "nigiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1157",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'deep red'?",
    "Answer": "makka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1158",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hirou'?",
    "Answer": "pick up"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1159",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mawasu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "turn",
      "rotate (something)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1160",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'no-to'?",
    "Answer": "notebook (loan word)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1161",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yameru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "resign",
      "leave (oneâ€™s job)",
      "quit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1162",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yureru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "shake",
      "sway"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1163",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rippa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fine",
      "elegant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1164",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'renshuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "practice",
      "training"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1165",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'divide'?",
    "Answer": "waru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1166",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'part'?",
    "Answer": "bubun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1167",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fuku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "wipe",
      "dry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1168",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'invite'?",
    "Answer": "maneku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1169",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "urgent",
      "steep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1170",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'become dirty'?",
    "Answer": "yogoreru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1171",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cross'?",
    "Answer": "wataru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1172",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tochuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "on the way",
      "half way"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1173",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'interview (loan word)'?",
    "Answer": "intabyu-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1174",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'steal'?",
    "Answer": "nusumu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1175",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'usual'?",
    "Answer": "fudan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1176",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ryokan'?",
    "Answer": "Japanese inn"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1177",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hakubutsukan'?",
    "Answer": "museum"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1178",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ho-mu'?",
    "Answer": "platform (for short)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1179",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hikkosu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "move",
      "relocate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1180",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'baggage'?",
    "Answer": "nimotsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1181",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rent'?",
    "Answer": "yachin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1182",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'plan'?",
    "Answer": "keikaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1183",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hallway'?",
    "Answer": "rouka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1184",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tenjou'?",
    "Answer": "ceiling"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1185",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'beddo'?",
    "Answer": "bed"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1186",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sofa'?",
    "Answer": "sofa-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1187",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'roof'?",
    "Answer": "yane"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1188",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'matsuri'?",
    "Answer": "festival"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1189",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rikon'?",
    "Answer": "divorce"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1190",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'leaf'?",
    "Answer": "ha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1191",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'light boat'?",
    "Answer": "bo-to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1192",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'moeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "burn",
      "catch on fire"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1193",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "roll up",
      "wrap"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1194",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'plastic'?",
    "Answer": "purasuchikku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1195",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'otozureru'?",
    "Answer": "go and visit (place)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1196",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tear'?",
    "Answer": "yaburu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1197",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'relation'?",
    "Answer": "kankei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1198",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rokuon'?",
    "Answer": "(sound) recording"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1199",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'unhappiness'?",
    "Answer": "fukou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1200",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gaikokugo'?",
    "Answer": "language"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1201",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'traditional Japanese clothes'?",
    "Answer": "kimono"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1202",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'milk'?",
    "Answer": "gyuunyuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1203",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ambulance'?",
    "Answer": "kyuukyuusha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1204",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fruit'?",
    "Answer": "kudamono"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1205",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mistake'?",
    "Answer": "machigai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1206",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'eigakan'?",
    "Answer": "movie theater"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1207",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kowai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "scary",
      "be afraid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1208",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mirror'?",
    "Answer": "kagami"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1209",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kusa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "grass",
      "weed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1210",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'polite speech'?",
    "Answer": "keigo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1211",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'absence'?",
    "Answer": "kesseki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1212",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suicchi'?",
    "Answer": "switch"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1213",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cleaning'?",
    "Answer": "souji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1214",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tatami'?",
    "Answer": "straw mat"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1215",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'speed'?",
    "Answer": "hayasa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1216",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hayashi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "woods",
      "forest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1217",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'purezento'?",
    "Answer": "present (loan word)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1218",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bentou'?",
    "Answer": "boxed lunch"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1219",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itsudemo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "at all times",
      "any time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1220",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sabishii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "lonely",
      "desolate",
      "sad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1221",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sukoshimo'?",
    "Answer": "(not) in the least"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1222",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'respect'?",
    "Answer": "sonkei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1223",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tennis'?",
    "Answer": "tenisu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1224",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'area'?",
    "Answer": "hirosa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1225",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'reading'?",
    "Answer": "yomi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1226",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'patience'?",
    "Answer": "gaman"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1227",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'nationality'?",
    "Answer": "kokuseki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1228",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'embarrassed'?",
    "Answer": "hazukashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1229",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'botan'?",
    "Answer": "button"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1230",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'youfuku'?",
    "Answer": "(western-style) clothes"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1231",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'oil'?",
    "Answer": "abura"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1232",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okashii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "funny",
      "comical"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1233",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'remain'?",
    "Answer": "amaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1234",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sports court'?",
    "Answer": "ko-to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1235",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'honest'?",
    "Answer": "shoujiki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1236",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dorama'?",
    "Answer": "drama"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1237",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'biza'?",
    "Answer": "visa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1238",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suidou'?",
    "Answer": "tap water"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1239",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tenin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "clerk",
      "salesperson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1240",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'battery'?",
    "Answer": "denchi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1241",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'poketto'?",
    "Answer": "pocket"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1242",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'handshake'?",
    "Answer": "akushu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1243",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'soon'?",
    "Answer": "sorosoro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1244",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'budou'?",
    "Answer": "grapes"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1245",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get lost'?",
    "Answer": "mayou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1246",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sightseeing'?",
    "Answer": "kenbutsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1247",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'let know'?",
    "Answer": "shiraseru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1248",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Shinto shrine'?",
    "Answer": "jinja"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1249",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chuusha'?",
    "Answer": [
      "injection",
      "shot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1250",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rarely'?",
    "Answer": "mettani"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1251",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakubun'?",
    "Answer": [
      "composition",
      "essay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1252",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sound'?",
    "Answer": "naru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1253",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'serious and sincere'?",
    "Answer": "majime"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1254",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'apply'?",
    "Answer": "moushikomu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1255",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'reizouko'?",
    "Answer": "refrigerator"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1256",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kiniiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "like",
      "be pleased with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1257",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kurisumasu'?",
    "Answer": "Christmas"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1258",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tie'?",
    "Answer": "nekutai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1259",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'birthday'?",
    "Answer": "tanjoubi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1260",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'single'?",
    "Answer": "dokushin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1261",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nigai'?",
    "Answer": "bitter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1262",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'baiorin'?",
    "Answer": "violin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1263",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'baggu'?",
    "Answer": "bag"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1264",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'until now'?",
    "Answer": "imamade"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1265",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kippu'?",
    "Answer": "ticket"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1266",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'elastic'?",
    "Answer": "gomu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1267",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shoushou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "a little",
      "a bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1268",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zuibun'?",
    "Answer": [
      "extremely",
      "considerably"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1269",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hipparu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pull",
      "drag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1270",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yakeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "burn",
      "cook"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1271",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'enpitsu'?",
    "Answer": "pencil"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1272",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'conversation'?",
    "Answer": "kaiwa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1273",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'guitar'?",
    "Answer": "gita-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1274",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tea'?",
    "Answer": "cha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1275",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atsusa'?",
    "Answer": "heat (of weather)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1276",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'i'?",
    "Answer": "stomach"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1277",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'non-smoking'?",
    "Answer": "kinen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1278",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'round'?",
    "Answer": "marui"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1279",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be photographed'?",
    "Answer": "utsuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1280",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'coffee shop'?",
    "Answer": "kissaten"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1281",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yappari'?",
    "Answer": [
      "just as I thought",
      "after all"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1282",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'weekly magazine'?",
    "Answer": "shuukanshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1283",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tana'?",
    "Answer": [
      "shelf",
      "rack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1284",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tremble'?",
    "Answer": "furueru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1285",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'migaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "polish",
      "grind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1286",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ka-ten'?",
    "Answer": "curtain"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1287",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fire'?",
    "Answer": "kaji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1288",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naifu'?",
    "Answer": "knife"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1289",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'minasan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "everybody",
      "everyone (polite)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1290",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ukeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "receive",
      "take",
      "undergo"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1291",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stick to",
      "cling to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1292",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'watakushi'?",
    "Answer": "I (formal)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1293",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kekkou'?",
    "Answer": "quite"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1294",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'slander'?",
    "Answer": "warukuchi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1295",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'spread'?",
    "Answer": "hiromaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1296",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naisho'?",
    "Answer": [
      "secrecy",
      "privacy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1297",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'close (eyes)'?",
    "Answer": "tsuburu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1298",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'youken'?",
    "Answer": [
      "matter",
      "things to be done"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1299",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'romanchikku'?",
    "Answer": "romantic"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1300",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'savings'?",
    "Answer": "chokin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1301",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'baiku'?",
    "Answer": "motorcycle"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1302",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'azukaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "take care of",
      "keep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1303",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'orenji'?",
    "Answer": "orange"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1304",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kamu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bite",
      "chew"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1305",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tight'?",
    "Answer": "kitsui"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1306",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "go over",
      "go across"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1307",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kodutsumi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "parcel",
      "package"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1308",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shinnen'?",
    "Answer": "new year"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1309",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'haitatsu'?",
    "Answer": "delivery"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1310",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'doubutsuen'?",
    "Answer": "zoo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1311",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'envelope'?",
    "Answer": "fuutou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1312",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'dangerous'?",
    "Answer": "abunai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1313",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'text'?",
    "Answer": "tekisuto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1314",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bini-ru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "plastic",
      "vinyl"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1315",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'album'?",
    "Answer": "arubamu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1316",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'swimming'?",
    "Answer": "suiei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1317",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'komu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be crowded",
      "be congested"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1318",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'skirt'?",
    "Answer": "suka-to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1319",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toreru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "come off",
      "be removed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1320",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pen'?",
    "Answer": "pen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1321",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mono'?",
    "Answer": [
      "thing",
      "object"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1322",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mail service'?",
    "Answer": "yuubin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1323",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wareru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "crack",
      "split"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1324",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'station attendant'?",
    "Answer": "ekiin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1325",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'talkative'?",
    "Answer": "oshaberi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1326",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'midoriiro'?",
    "Answer": "green color"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1327",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'every morning'?",
    "Answer": "maiasa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1328",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mageru'?",
    "Answer": "bend (something)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1329",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kitto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "surely",
      "certainly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1330",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'science (school subject)'?",
    "Answer": "rika"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1331",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shitagi'?",
    "Answer": "underwear"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1332",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'futoru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "grow fat",
      "gain weight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1333",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'air conditioning (cooling)'?",
    "Answer": "reibou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1334",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wakareru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "separate",
      "part"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1335",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'aku'?",
    "Answer": "become available or vacant"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1336",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'go out'?",
    "Answer": "dekakeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1337",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maiban'?",
    "Answer": "every evening"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1338",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ring'?",
    "Answer": "yubiwa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1339",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kusaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "rot",
      "go bad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1340",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'poverty'?",
    "Answer": "binbou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1341",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oshare'?",
    "Answer": [
      "trendy",
      "fashionable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1342",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'break'?",
    "Answer": "kyuukei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1343",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shita'?",
    "Answer": "tongue"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1344",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'juice'?",
    "Answer": "ju-su"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1345",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zero'?",
    "Answer": [
      "zero",
      "none (loan word)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1346",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'morning edition paper'?",
    "Answer": "choukan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1347",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'teinei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "polite",
      "careful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1348",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'not good at'?",
    "Answer": "nigate"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1349",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(specific) day'?",
    "Answer": "hi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1350",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hikkoshi'?",
    "Answer": "moving (house)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1351",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hodou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sidewalk",
      "pavement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1352",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'break'?",
    "Answer": "oreru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1353",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'send-off'?",
    "Answer": "miokuri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1354",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yuukan'?",
    "Answer": "evening edition paper"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1355",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the other day'?",
    "Answer": "konoaida"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1356",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hieru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "cool down",
      "get chilled"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1357",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pinku'?",
    "Answer": "pink"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1358",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gurasu'?",
    "Answer": "glass"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1359",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ke'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hair",
      "down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1360",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kokuban'?",
    "Answer": "blackboard"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1361",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pile up'?",
    "Answer": "tsumoru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1362",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'half a year'?",
    "Answer": "hantoshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1363",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'genzai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "the present",
      "present time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1364",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'riyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "utilization",
      "usage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1365",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'method'?",
    "Answer": "houhou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1366",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chuushin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "center (of a circle",
      "etc.)",
      "core"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1367",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'akiraka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "clear",
      "obvious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1368",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shachou'?",
    "Answer": "president (of a company)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1369",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'almost'?",
    "Answer": "hobo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1370",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shouhin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "goods",
      "commodities"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1371",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oogata'?",
    "Answer": [
      "large",
      "large scale"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1372",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kagiru'?",
    "Answer": "be limited to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1373",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'record'?",
    "Answer": "kiroku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1374",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'concrete'?",
    "Answer": "gutaiteki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1375",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'effect'?",
    "Answer": "kouka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1376",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'opening (to the public)'?",
    "Answer": "koukai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1377",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakuhin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "work of art",
      "creation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1378",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'semaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "close in on",
      "approach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1379",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taikai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tournament",
      "event"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1380",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'background'?",
    "Answer": "haikei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1381",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'character'?",
    "Answer": "moji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1382",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rule'?",
    "Answer": "kisoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1383",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'neighborhood'?",
    "Answer": "kinjo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1384",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'chart'?",
    "Answer": "gurapu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1385",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'capital'?",
    "Answer": "shuto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1386",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'herasu'?",
    "Answer": "reduce (something)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1387",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kakureru'?",
    "Answer": "hide"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1388",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bijutsukan'?",
    "Answer": "art museum"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1389",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'baka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "foolish",
      "stupid"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1390",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hima'?",
    "Answer": [
      "free time",
      "spare time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1391",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ehagaki'?",
    "Answer": "picture postcard"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1392",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'annani'?",
    "Answer": [
      "that much",
      "such"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1393",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "going",
      "bound for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1394",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'commute'?",
    "Answer": "tsuukin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1395",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'correctly'?",
    "Answer": "chanto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1396",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nonbiri'?",
    "Answer": "take it easy"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1397",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kinchou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tension",
      "strain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1398",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kiduku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "notice",
      "realize"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1399",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'monogatari'?",
    "Answer": [
      "story",
      "tale"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1400",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'deguchi'?",
    "Answer": "exit"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1401",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'climb'?",
    "Answer": "noboru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1402",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'masshiro'?",
    "Answer": "pure-white"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1403",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bring down'?",
    "Answer": "orosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1404",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kashidasu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "lend",
      "lend out"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1405",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'soccer'?",
    "Answer": "sakka-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1406",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'heating'?",
    "Answer": "danbou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1407",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tebukuro'?",
    "Answer": "gloves"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1408",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'not at home'?",
    "Answer": "rusu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1409",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lie'?",
    "Answer": "uso"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1410",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'enryo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "restraint",
      "hold back"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1411",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "break (something)",
      "fold (something)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1412",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'su-pu'?",
    "Answer": "soup"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1413",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'banana'?",
    "Answer": "banana"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1414",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kawaisou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "poor",
      "pitiful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1415",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'police car'?",
    "Answer": "patoka-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1416",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hanba-ga-'?",
    "Answer": "hamburger"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1417",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'moufu'?",
    "Answer": "blanket"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1418",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'escalator'?",
    "Answer": "esukare-ta-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1419",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'young lady'?",
    "Answer": "ojousan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1420",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pocket notebook'?",
    "Answer": "techou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1421",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taoru'?",
    "Answer": "towel"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1422",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'baiten'?",
    "Answer": [
      "booth",
      "shop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1423",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pachiko'?",
    "Answer": "pachinko (Japanese pinball)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1424",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'apologize'?",
    "Answer": "ayamaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1425",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cake'?",
    "Answer": "ke-ki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1426",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tenkiyohou'?",
    "Answer": "weather forecast"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1427",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "strange",
      "weird"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1428",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'isshoukenmei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hard-working",
      "doing oneâ€™s best"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1429",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'make a mistake'?",
    "Answer": "machigau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1430",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jimushitsu'?",
    "Answer": "office"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1431",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'suit'?",
    "Answer": "su-tsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1432",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ticket (loan word)'?",
    "Answer": "chiketto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1433",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chokore-to'?",
    "Answer": "chocolate"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1434",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nugu'?",
    "Answer": "take off (clothes)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1435",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'New Yearâ€™s card'?",
    "Answer": "nenkajou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1436",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'vehicle'?",
    "Answer": "norimono"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1437",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'futon'?",
    "Answer": "Japanese-style padded mattress"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1438",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be useful'?",
    "Answer": "yakunitatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1439",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tear'?",
    "Answer": "yabureru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1440",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'youji'?",
    "Answer": [
      "errand",
      "business"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1441",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'copy'?",
    "Answer": "utsusu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1442",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'udedokei'?",
    "Answer": "wrist watch"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1443",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'present'?",
    "Answer": "okurimono"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1444",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'channeru'?",
    "Answer": "channel"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1445",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hiyasu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "chill (something)",
      "cool down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1446",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'put in order'?",
    "Answer": "katazukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1447",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanpai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "toast",
      "drink (in celebration)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1448",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stop (of a train)'?",
    "Answer": "teisha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1449",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'naku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sing",
      "cry (of animals)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1450",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'gas station'?",
    "Answer": "gasorinsutando"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1451",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'one way (trip)'?",
    "Answer": "katamichi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1452",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'police box'?",
    "Answer": "kouban"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1453",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'greatly'?",
    "Answer": "daibu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1454",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'de-to'?",
    "Answer": [
      "date",
      "romantic meeting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1455",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rainy season'?",
    "Answer": "tsuyu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1456",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'massugu'?",
    "Answer": "straight"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1457",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lemon'?",
    "Answer": "remon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1458",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'outerwear'?",
    "Answer": "uwagi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1459",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'erai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "great",
      "eminent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1460",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'how to write'?",
    "Answer": "kakikata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1461",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cook (rice)'?",
    "Answer": "taku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1462",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cheese'?",
    "Answer": "chi-zu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1463",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'doraibu'?",
    "Answer": "drive (loan word)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1464",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fumikiri'?",
    "Answer": "railroad crossing"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1465",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'racket'?",
    "Answer": "raketto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1466",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'uketsuke'?",
    "Answer": [
      "receptionist",
      "information office"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1467",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okoru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "get angry",
      "scold"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1468",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'keshou'?",
    "Answer": "makeup"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1469",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'convenience'?",
    "Answer": "tsugou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1470",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hige'?",
    "Answer": [
      "beard",
      "moustache"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1471",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hondana'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bookshelf",
      "bookcase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1472",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pitch-dark'?",
    "Answer": "makkura"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1473",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'boil'?",
    "Answer": "waku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1474",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sell out'?",
    "Answer": "urikireru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1475",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oshiire'?",
    "Answer": "sliding-door closet"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1476",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'leather'?",
    "Answer": "kawa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1477",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gussuri'?",
    "Answer": "soundly"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1478",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koucha'?",
    "Answer": "black tea"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1479",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jama'?",
    "Answer": [
      "disturbance",
      "blocking"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1480",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'so-su'?",
    "Answer": "sauce"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1481",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tasu'?",
    "Answer": "add (things of the same kind)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1482",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tomato'?",
    "Answer": "tomato"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1483",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'butter'?",
    "Answer": "bata-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1484",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'departure (of a vehicle)'?",
    "Answer": "hassha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1485",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'volleyball'?",
    "Answer": "bare-ho-ru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1486",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'dishes to go with the rice'?",
    "Answer": "okazu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1487",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'karenda-'?",
    "Answer": "calendar"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1488",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tonikaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "in any case",
      "anyway"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1489",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tanoshimi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "enjoyment",
      "something looked forward to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1490",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oshaberi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "chatter",
      "idle talk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1491",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'reading books'?",
    "Answer": "dokusho"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1492",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'chill'?",
    "Answer": "samuke"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1493",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sunset glow'?",
    "Answer": "yuuyake"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1494",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itameru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "damage",
      "hurt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1495",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kusuguttai'?",
    "Answer": "ticklish"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1496",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dorobou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "thief",
      "burglar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1497",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'paper sliding door'?",
    "Answer": "fusuma"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1498",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bijin'?",
    "Answer": "beautiful woman"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1499",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taipuraita-'?",
    "Answer": "typewriter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1500",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the year after next'?",
    "Answer": "sarainen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1501",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'joke'?",
    "Answer": "joudan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1502",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chikaduku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "approach",
      "come close"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1503",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'denwachou'?",
    "Answer": "telephone book"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1504",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'beru'?",
    "Answer": "bell"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1505",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hang (something) out to dry'?",
    "Answer": "hosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1506",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'amount of money'?",
    "Answer": "kingaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1507",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ka'?",
    "Answer": "mosquito"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1508",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'feel sad'?",
    "Answer": "kanashimu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1509",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'air conditioner (cooling)'?",
    "Answer": "ku-ra-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1510",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rudeness'?",
    "Answer": "shitsurei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1511",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'washing machine'?",
    "Answer": "sentakuki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1512",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tofu'?",
    "Answer": "toufu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1513",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hirune'?",
    "Answer": "nap"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1514",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fuben'?",
    "Answer": "inconvenient"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1515",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'milk (loan word)'?",
    "Answer": "miruku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1516",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mukougawa'?",
    "Answer": "other side"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1517",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hundred million'?",
    "Answer": "oku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1518",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'orei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "thanks",
      "gratitude"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1519",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kiseru'?",
    "Answer": "dress (someone)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1520",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sarada'?",
    "Answer": "salad"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1521",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaeru'?",
    "Answer": "substitute for"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1522",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shikaku'?",
    "Answer": "square"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1523",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyukou'?",
    "Answer": "express train"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1524",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kousaten'?",
    "Answer": [
      "crossing",
      "intersection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1525",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'awake'?",
    "Answer": "sameru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1526",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lunch break'?",
    "Answer": "hiruyasumi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1527",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'beruto'?",
    "Answer": "belt"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1528",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'black'?",
    "Answer": "makkuro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1529",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'everyone'?",
    "Answer": "minasama"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1530",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ra-men'?",
    "Answer": "ramen (Chinese noodles)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1531",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lighter'?",
    "Answer": "raita-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1532",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'waishatsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "business shirt",
      "dress shirt"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1533",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'korobu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fall down",
      "fall over"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1534",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shower'?",
    "Answer": "shawa-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1535",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'electric fan'?",
    "Answer": "senpuuki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1536",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chikoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tardiness",
      "lateness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1537",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fish",
      "catch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1538",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Japanese wheat noodles'?",
    "Answer": "udon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1539",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'kana'?",
    "Answer": "kana"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1540",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'memorial day'?",
    "Answer": "kinenbi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1541",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'downhill'?",
    "Answer": "kudari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1542",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'notice board'?",
    "Answer": "keijiban"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1543",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'freeze'?",
    "Answer": "kooru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1544",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gomi'?",
    "Answer": "trash"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1545",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'su-pa-ma-ketto'?",
    "Answer": "supermarket"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1546",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'burabura'?",
    "Answer": [
      "wander",
      "walk around"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1547",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'announcer'?",
    "Answer": "anaunsa-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1548",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jisui'?",
    "Answer": "cooking (for oneself)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1549",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tomeru'?",
    "Answer": "stop (something/someone)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1550",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toshishita'?",
    "Answer": [
      "younger",
      "junior"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1551",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cure (something)'?",
    "Answer": "naosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1552",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'chopsticks'?",
    "Answer": "hashi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1553",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hanami'?",
    "Answer": "flower viewing"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1554",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'drawer'?",
    "Answer": "hikidashi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1555",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yaku'?",
    "Answer": "translation"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1556",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'how'?",
    "Answer": "ikaga"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1557",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koutsuuhi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "traveling expense",
      "transportation fee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1558",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sutereo'?",
    "Answer": "stereo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1559",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'saikai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "meeting again",
      "reunion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1560",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suberu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "slide",
      "slip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1561",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'speaking fast'?",
    "Answer": "hayakuchi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1562",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'turn over'?",
    "Answer": "uragaesu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1563",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kado'?",
    "Answer": [
      "corner",
      "edge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1564",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kirakira'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sparkling",
      "glittering"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1565",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sankaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "figure",
      "area etc."
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1566",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hageshii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "violent",
      "intense"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1567",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'management'?",
    "Answer": "keiei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1568",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'magnification'?",
    "Answer": "kakudai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1569",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'posture'?",
    "Answer": "shisei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1570",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shuuhen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "area",
      "region"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1571",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ta'?",
    "Answer": "other (Chinese origin)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1572",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tassuru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "attain",
      "reach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1573",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'at that time'?",
    "Answer": "touji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1574",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'natural'?",
    "Answer": "touzen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1575",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nouryoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "capability",
      "performance ability of machine",
      "etc."
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1576",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'handan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "judgment",
      "decision"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1577",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sugiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pass by",
      "go past"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1578",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seikaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "accurate",
      "precise"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1579",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'war between countries'?",
    "Answer": "sensou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1580",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'broadcasting'?",
    "Answer": "housou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1581",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'custom'?",
    "Answer": "shuukan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1582",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'film'?",
    "Answer": "fuirumu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1583",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'uketsukeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "receive",
      "accept"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1584",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'dance'?",
    "Answer": "dansu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1585",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'this much'?",
    "Answer": "konnani"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1586",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fuku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "blow",
      "play (a wind instrument)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1587",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'well (interjection)'?",
    "Answer": "Maa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1588",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'e-mail'?",
    "Answer": "me-ru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1589",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Internet'?",
    "Answer": "inta-netto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1590",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'come from'?",
    "Answer": "shusshin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1591",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'occupation'?",
    "Answer": "shokugyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1592",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'suta-'?",
    "Answer": "star"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1593",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kudaranai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "worthless",
      "trifling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1594",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'name list'?",
    "Answer": "Meibo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1595",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Tsuujou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "common",
      "usually",
      "typically"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1596",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanai'?",
    "Answer": "oneâ€™s wife"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1597",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Shoubousho'?",
    "Answer": "fire station"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1598",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Futatabi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "again",
      "a second time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1599",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'president (of a country)'?",
    "Answer": "Daitouryou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1600",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'entrance ticket'?",
    "Answer": "Nyuujouken"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1601",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nekkuresu'?",
    "Answer": "necklace"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1602",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pajama'?",
    "Answer": "pajamas"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1603",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ballpoint pen'?",
    "Answer": "Borupen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1604",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kayui'?",
    "Answer": "itchy"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1605",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'samasu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "awaken",
      "wake up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1606",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Suika'?",
    "Answer": "watermelon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1607",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'buckwheat noodles'?",
    "Answer": "Soba"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1608",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tokkyuu'?",
    "Answer": "super-express"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1609",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'glue'?",
    "Answer": "Nori"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1610",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'generally'?",
    "Answer": "____"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1611",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'basukettobo-ru'?",
    "Answer": "basketball"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1612",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get drunk'?",
    "Answer": "yopparau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1613",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Dokidoki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "feel excited",
      "feel nervous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1614",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'want'?",
    "Answer": "hoshigaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1615",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Hayaoki'?",
    "Answer": "getting up early"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1616",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'miso soup'?",
    "Answer": "misoshiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1617",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yomikata'?",
    "Answer": [
      "how to read",
      "way of reading"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1618",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iriguchi'?",
    "Answer": "entrance"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1619",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'orosu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "unload",
      "set down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1620",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kakaru'?",
    "Answer": "hang"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1621",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sandoicchi'?",
    "Answer": "sandwich"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1622",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'square-shaped'?",
    "Answer": "Shikakui"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1623",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsukiataru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "run into",
      "come to the end (of a road)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1624",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kawakasu'?",
    "Answer": "dry (something)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1625",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Teikiken'?",
    "Answer": "commuter pass"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1626",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nikoniko'?",
    "Answer": [
      "smilingly",
      "keep smiling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1627",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'go down'?",
    "Answer": "kudaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1628",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wool'?",
    "Answer": "wu-ru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1629",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cola'?",
    "Answer": "ko-ra"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1630",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'toilet paper'?",
    "Answer": "Toirettopepa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1631",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'norikae'?",
    "Answer": [
      "transfer",
      "change (trains)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1632",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'haizara'?",
    "Answer": "ashtray"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1633",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hamu'?",
    "Answer": "ham"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1634",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'floor'?",
    "Answer": "yuka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1635",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Ro-maji'?",
    "Answer": "Roman alphabet"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1636",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ichigo'?",
    "Answer": "strawberry"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1637",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'curry rice'?",
    "Answer": "kareaisu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1638",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cash card'?",
    "Answer": "Kyasshukado"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1639",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(bus) stop'?",
    "Answer": "teiryuujo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1640",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'barber'?",
    "Answer": "tokoya"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1641",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'brushing oneâ€™s teeth'?",
    "Answer": "hamigaki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1642",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of '____'?",
    "Answer": [
      "evening meal",
      "dinner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1643",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yopparai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "drunkard",
      "drunk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1644",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Rei'?",
    "Answer": "example"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1645",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Ojigi'?",
    "Answer": "bow"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1646",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pedestrian crossing'?",
    "Answer": "Oudan hodou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1647",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shaky'?",
    "Answer": "guragura"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1648",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Koukuubin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "airmail",
      "airfreight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1649",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Jamu'?",
    "Answer": "jam"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1650",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'slippers'?",
    "Answer": "Surippa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1651",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tatamu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fold",
      "shut",
      "close"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1652",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toranpu'?",
    "Answer": "playing cards"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1653",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hikage'?",
    "Answer": "shade of the sun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1654",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bunbougu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stationery",
      "writing materials"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1655",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'menkyoshou'?",
    "Answer": "license"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1656",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yakusu'?",
    "Answer": "translate"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1657",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'all right'?",
    "Answer": "yoroshii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1658",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'money exchange'?",
    "Answer": "ryougae"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1659",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be put in order'?",
    "Answer": "kataduku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1660",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kappu'?",
    "Answer": "cup"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1661",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'keshigomi'?",
    "Answer": "eraser"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1662",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'skate'?",
    "Answer": "suketo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1663",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nabe'?",
    "Answer": "pan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1664",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nebou'?",
    "Answer": "oversleeping"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1665",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hasami'?",
    "Answer": "scissors"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1666",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'massao'?",
    "Answer": [
      "deep-blue",
      "pale"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1667",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'make (something) dirty'?",
    "Answer": "yogosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1668",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'something left behind'?",
    "Answer": "wasuremono"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1669",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'multiplication'?",
    "Answer": "kakezan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1670",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stinky'?",
    "Answer": "kusai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1671",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsukiatari'?",
    "Answer": "end of a street"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1672",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'scarf'?",
    "Answer": "mafura-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1673",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'peach'?",
    "Answer": "momo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1674",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'accessories'?",
    "Answer": "akusesari-"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1675",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'yawn'?",
    "Answer": "akubi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1676",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'candy'?",
    "Answer": "ame"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1677",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'going up'?",
    "Answer": "nobori"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1678",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'narubeku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "asâ€¦as possible",
      "if possible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1679",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'without moving'?",
    "Answer": "jitto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1680",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shokki'?",
    "Answer": "tableware"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1681",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nobasu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "extend",
      "postpone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1682",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yakkyoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "drugstore",
      "pharmacy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1683",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'male (animal)'?",
    "Answer": "osu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1684",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'female (animal)'?",
    "Answer": "mesu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1685",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wafuu'?",
    "Answer": "Japanese inspired"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1686",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ibiki'?",
    "Answer": "snoring"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1687",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'picnic'?",
    "Answer": "pikunikku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1688",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'region'?",
    "Answer": "chiiki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1689",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'misunderstanding'?",
    "Answer": "kanchigai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1690",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'juuyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "important",
      "essential"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1691",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'oneâ€™s husband'?",
    "Answer": "shujin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1692",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'otaku'?",
    "Answer": "(someone elseâ€™s) home"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1693",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hiking'?",
    "Answer": "haikingu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1694",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hatake'?",
    "Answer": [
      "field",
      "farm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1695",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'boyfriend'?",
    "Answer": "boifurendo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1696",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iyaringu'?",
    "Answer": "earrings"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1697",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'girlfriend'?",
    "Answer": "ga-rufurendo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1698",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'soft'?",
    "Answer": "yawaraka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1699",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'natto'?",
    "Answer": "fermented soybeans"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1700",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Betsuni'?",
    "Answer": [
      "particularly",
      "not really"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1701",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Doushitemo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "by any means",
      "really"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1702",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'father'?",
    "Answer": "chichioya"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1703",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sasou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "invite",
      "ask out"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1704",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hahaoya'?",
    "Answer": [
      "mother",
      "female parent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1705",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hirumae'?",
    "Answer": [
      "in the morning",
      "before noon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1706",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be dizzy'?",
    "Answer": "furafura"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1707",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kobosu'?",
    "Answer": "spill (something)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1708",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bring'?",
    "Answer": "mottekuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1709",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Furimuku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "turn around",
      "look back"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1710",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Senmenjou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "washroom",
      "bathroom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1711",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sotogawa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "exterior",
      "outside"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1712",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dandan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "gradually",
      "little by little"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1713",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wrap'?",
    "Answer": "tsutsumu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1714",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get lost'?",
    "Answer": "nakunaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1715",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pig'?",
    "Answer": "buta"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1716",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'homeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "praise",
      "compliment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1717",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wakasu'?",
    "Answer": "boil (water)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1718",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atatameru'?",
    "Answer": "warm (something) up"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1719",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'exchange'?",
    "Answer": "kaeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1720",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cheap-looking'?",
    "Answer": "yasuppoi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1721",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'giragira'?",
    "Answer": [
      "glaring",
      "blinding"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1722",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nantoka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "somehow",
      "please"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1723",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iyoiyo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "finally",
      "any moment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1724",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'not crowded'?",
    "Answer": "garagara"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1725",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'canned food'?",
    "Answer": "kantzume"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1726",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'injury'?",
    "Answer": "kega"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1727",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'samusa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "coldness",
      "cold"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1728",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'holiday'?",
    "Answer": "shukujitsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1729",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sukiyaki'?",
    "Answer": "Sukiyaki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1730",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hagaki'?",
    "Answer": "postcard"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1731",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'haku'?",
    "Answer": "sweep"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1732",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nanishiro'?",
    "Answer": [
      "anyhow",
      "as you may know"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1733",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dondon'?",
    "Answer": [
      "quickly",
      "rapidly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1734",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pekopeko'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hungry",
      "starving"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1735",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fluently'?",
    "Answer": "perapera"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1736",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'reinkoto'?",
    "Answer": "raincoat"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1737",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ice cream (for short)'?",
    "Answer": "aisu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1738",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'salty'?",
    "Answer": "shiokarai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1739",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'serote-pu'?",
    "Answer": "scotch tape"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1740",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'drastically'?",
    "Answer": "oohaba"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1741",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'education'?",
    "Answer": "Kyouiku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1742",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Kouji'?",
    "Answer": [
      "construction",
      "repairing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1743",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tantou'?",
    "Answer": "person in charge (of official duties)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1744",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Houritsu'?",
    "Answer": "law"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1745",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "circle",
      "round"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1746",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'happyo'?",
    "Answer": "announcement"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1747",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kenkyuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "research",
      "study"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1748",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ippou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "one way",
      "the other party"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1749",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'domestic'?",
    "Answer": "kokunai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1750",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'whole'?",
    "Answer": "zentai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1751",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nochi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "after",
      "afterward"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1752",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ningen'?",
    "Answer": "human being"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1753",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sliced raw fish or meat'?",
    "Answer": "sashimi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1754",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rose'?",
    "Answer": "Bara"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1755",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nezumi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "rat",
      "mouse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1756",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'below'?",
    "Answer": "ika"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1757",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mukashi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "old times",
      "the old days"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1758",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wake'?",
    "Answer": [
      "reason",
      "sense"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1759",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chigai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "difference",
      "mistake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1760",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shikkari'?",
    "Answer": [
      "mature",
      "responsible"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1761",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Shourai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "future",
      "in the future"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1762",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fushigi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "mystery",
      "wonder"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1763",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'never'?",
    "Answer": "kesshite"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1764",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'failure'?",
    "Answer": "shippai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1765",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ban'?",
    "Answer": [
      "oneâ€™s turn",
      "watch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1766",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'meet'?",
    "Answer": "deau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1767",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be troubled'?",
    "Answer": "nayamu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1768",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ase'?",
    "Answer": "sweat"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1769",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'all'?",
    "Answer": "sukkari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1770",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'substitution'?",
    "Answer": "kawari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1771",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hitokoto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "single word",
      "brief speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1772",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yutaka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "rich",
      "ample"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1773",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'setsuzoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "connection",
      "joining"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1774",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kakaeru'?",
    "Answer": "hold in oneâ€™s arms"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1775",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'enjin'?",
    "Answer": "engine"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1776",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shoujo'?",
    "Answer": "young girl"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1777",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'muda'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pointless",
      "waste"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1778",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'automatic operation'?",
    "Answer": "jidou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1779",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'senpai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "senior",
      "superior"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1780",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nagameru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "look out",
      "gaze"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1781",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Shorui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "documents",
      "papers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1782",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nengetsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "years",
      "period of time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1783",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'moyasu'?",
    "Answer": "burn (something)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1784",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'senro'?",
    "Answer": [
      "railway track",
      "line"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1785",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bathing suit'?",
    "Answer": "mizugi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1786",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kawairashii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "lovely",
      "charming"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1787",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'good friend'?",
    "Answer": "nakayoshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1788",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'umeboshi'?",
    "Answer": "pickled plum"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1789",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'doresu'?",
    "Answer": "formal dress"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1790",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsukusu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "make utmost efforts",
      "devote to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1791",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the earth'?",
    "Answer": "chikyuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1792",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'unkind'?",
    "Answer": "fushinsetsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1793",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'very thirsty'?",
    "Answer": "karakara"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1794",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bookcase'?",
    "Answer": "honbako"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1795",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'horizontal writing'?",
    "Answer": "yokogaki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1796",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sobaya'?",
    "Answer": "buckwheat noodle shop"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1797",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'processing'?",
    "Answer": "kakou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1798",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'experiment'?",
    "Answer": "jikken"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1799",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'love'?",
    "Answer": "aisuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1800",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(not) that much'?",
    "Answer": "anmari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1801",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'all of a sudden'?",
    "Answer": "ikinari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1802",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'front'?",
    "Answer": "omote"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1803",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yogore'?",
    "Answer": [
      "dirt",
      "blot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1804",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'interval'?",
    "Answer": "aida"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1805",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'purple'?",
    "Answer": "murasaki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1806",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ash color'?",
    "Answer": "haiiro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1807",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chi'?",
    "Answer": "blood (colloquial)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1808",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'jaw'?",
    "Answer": "ago"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1809",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hajimeni'?",
    "Answer": [
      "in the beginning",
      "first"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1810",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atatameru'?",
    "Answer": "get warm"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1811",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'compliment'?",
    "Answer": "oseji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1812",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fukuro'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bag",
      "sack"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1813",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'long sleeves'?",
    "Answer": "nagasode"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1814",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hansode'?",
    "Answer": "short sleeves"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1815",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shape'?",
    "Answer": "katachi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1816",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'keshiki'?",
    "Answer": "natural scenery or landscape"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1817",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pouring'?",
    "Answer": "zaazaa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1818",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'saraigetsu'?",
    "Answer": "the month after next"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1819",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'let (someone) stay over'?",
    "Answer": "tomeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1820",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'scold'?",
    "Answer": "shikaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1821",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'make a noise'?",
    "Answer": "sawagu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1822",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'road'?",
    "Answer": "Shadou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1823",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Soujiki'?",
    "Answer": "vacuum cleaner"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1824",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shave'?",
    "Answer": "soru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1825",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'haru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stick",
      "paste",
      "put"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1826",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stand",
      "table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1827",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mostly'?",
    "Answer": "omoni"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1828",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'knock down'?",
    "Answer": "taosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1829",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'star'?",
    "Answer": "hoshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1830",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'choujo'?",
    "Answer": "eldest daughter"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1831",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'nail'?",
    "Answer": "tsume"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1832",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'can'?",
    "Answer": "kan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1833",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tonton'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tapping",
      "patting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1834",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sleeve'?",
    "Answer": "sode"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1835",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get wet'?",
    "Answer": "nureru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1836",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'percent'?",
    "Answer": "pa-sento"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1837",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'go up'?",
    "Answer": "agaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1838",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hakushu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "applause",
      "clapping"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1839",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'play (instruments)'?",
    "Answer": "hiku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1840",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'laces'?",
    "Answer": "himo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1841",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'early afternoon'?",
    "Answer": "hirusugi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1842",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fune'?",
    "Answer": [
      "ship",
      "vessel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1843",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "scatter",
      "sprinkle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1844",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mei'?",
    "Answer": "niece"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1845",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'individual person'?",
    "Answer": "kojin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1846",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'singer'?",
    "Answer": "kashu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1847",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Shain'?",
    "Answer": [
      "staff member",
      "employee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1848",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'real estate agent'?",
    "Answer": "fudousanya"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1849",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'biggest'?",
    "Answer": "saidai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1850",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ugoki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "movement",
      "motion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1851",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'affair'?",
    "Answer": "jiken"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1852",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the past'?",
    "Answer": "kako"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1853",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cooperation'?",
    "Answer": "kyouryoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1854",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'time'?",
    "Answer": "jiki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1855",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tatsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pass",
      "elapse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1856",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'thunder'?",
    "Answer": "kaminari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1857",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'responsibility'?",
    "Answer": "sekinin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1858",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wish'?",
    "Answer": "negau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1859",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'discovery'?",
    "Answer": "hakken"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1860",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "spirit",
      "temperament"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1861",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hair salon'?",
    "Answer": "byouin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1862",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'state of affairs'?",
    "Answer": "joukyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1863",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mokuteki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "objective",
      "purpose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1864",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'corporation'?",
    "Answer": "kigyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1865",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuri'?",
    "Answer": "fishing"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1866",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'comics'?",
    "Answer": "manga"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1867",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hot spring'?",
    "Answer": "onsen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1868",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tore-ningu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "training",
      "workout"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1869",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'gossip'?",
    "Answer": "uwasa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1870",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'honmono'?",
    "Answer": [
      "real",
      "truly worthy (things",
      "people)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1871",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'aidea'?",
    "Answer": "idea"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1872",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chika'?",
    "Answer": "underground"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1873",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'market'?",
    "Answer": "ma-ketto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1874",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'schedule (loan word)'?",
    "Answer": "sukeju-ru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1875",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shucchou'?",
    "Answer": "business trip"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1876",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cook'?",
    "Answer": "kokku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1877",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'noon'?",
    "Answer": "shougo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1878",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'brush'?",
    "Answer": "burashi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1879",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'write down'?",
    "Answer": "kakitoru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1880",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kangei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "welcome",
      "greet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1881",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'development'?",
    "Answer": "kaihatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1882",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yuubinyasan'?",
    "Answer": "mail carrier"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1883",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'president'?",
    "Answer": "kaichou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1884",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kin'?",
    "Answer": "gold"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1885",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ashes'?",
    "Answer": "hai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1886",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bone'?",
    "Answer": "hone"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1887",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'furoya'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bathhouse",
      "public bath"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1888",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'komaka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "small",
      "fine",
      "detailed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1889",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'going'?",
    "Answer": "yuki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1890",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hitobito'?",
    "Answer": "people"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1891",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tera'?",
    "Answer": "temple"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1892",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rooster'?",
    "Answer": "niwatori"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1893",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'minato'?",
    "Answer": [
      "port",
      "harbor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1894",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'move'?",
    "Answer": "utsuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1895",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'differ'?",
    "Answer": "kotonaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1896",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'offer'?",
    "Answer": "teikyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1897",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'citizens'?",
    "Answer": "shimin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1898",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanja'?",
    "Answer": "patient"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1899",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gantan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "morning of the January 1st",
      "New Yearâ€™s Day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1900",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yawarakai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "soft",
      "gentle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1901",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'suit'?",
    "Answer": "niau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1902",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tashikameru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "check",
      "confirm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1903",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'senaka'?",
    "Answer": "(oneâ€™s) back"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1904",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hada'?",
    "Answer": [
      "human skin",
      "surface"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1905",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'order'?",
    "Answer": "junban"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1906",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'matomo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sane",
      "reasonable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1907",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'exactly right'?",
    "Answer": "pittari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1908",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'unintentionally'?",
    "Answer": "omowazu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1909",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yori'?",
    "Answer": [
      "even more ~",
      "even less ~"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1910",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wasteful'?",
    "Answer": "mottainai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1911",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'information'?",
    "Answer": "jouhou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1912",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'akirameru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "abandon",
      "give up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1913",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'natsukashii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fondly-remembered",
      "long-forgotten"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1914",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'suspicious'?",
    "Answer": "ayashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1915",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shimesu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "show",
      "indicate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1916",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fully'?",
    "Answer": "tappuri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1917",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sassoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "immediately",
      "right away"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1918",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'guuzen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "by chance",
      "coincidence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1919",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuduki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "continuation",
      "sequel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1920",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sum'?",
    "Answer": "goukei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1921",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kizu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "wound",
      "scar"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1922",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'troublesome'?",
    "Answer": "mendou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1923",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'guai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "condition",
      "health"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1924",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chuushi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "suspension",
      "cancellation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1925",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tetsuduki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "procedure",
      "proceeding"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1926",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'result'?",
    "Answer": "kekka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1927",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kensetsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "construction (of a building",
      "road",
      "bridge",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1928",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hanbai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sale",
      "selling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1929",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kinou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "function",
      "feature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1930",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koro'?",
    "Answer": [
      "time",
      "the time when ~"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1931",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Nicchuu'?",
    "Answer": "during the day"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1932",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Kongo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "in the future",
      "from now on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1933",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'eikyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "influence",
      "effect"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1934",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'field'?",
    "Answer": "bunya"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1935",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kansuru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "relate to",
      "regarding"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1936",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'state'?",
    "Answer": "joutai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1937",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'price'?",
    "Answer": "kakaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1938",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sugata'?",
    "Answer": [
      "figure",
      "appearance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1939",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kitai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "expectation",
      "anticipation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1940",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'remove'?",
    "Answer": "nozoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1941",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'general'?",
    "Answer": "ippan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1942",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hyougen'?",
    "Answer": "expression"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1943",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kansei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "completion",
      "finish making or building something"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1944",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'henka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "change",
      "alteration"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1945",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'participation'?",
    "Answer": "sanka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1946",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'land'?",
    "Answer": "tochi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1947",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'examination and consideration'?",
    "Answer": "kentou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1948",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaishi'?",
    "Answer": "beginning"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1949",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sonaete'?",
    "Answer": [
      "provide for",
      "prepare for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1950",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'content'?",
    "Answer": "naiyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1951",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ataeru'?",
    "Answer": "give (formal)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1952",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hirogaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "spread out",
      "extend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1953",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fact'?",
    "Answer": "jijitsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1954",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'decision'?",
    "Answer": "kettei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1955",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'juutaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "housing",
      "residence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1956",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'daihyou'?",
    "Answer": "representative"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1957",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'meirei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "command",
      "order"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1958",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tachiba'?",
    "Answer": [
      "standpoint",
      "position"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1959",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'Nao'?",
    "Answer": [
      "still",
      "in addition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1960",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'calculation'?",
    "Answer": "keisan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1961",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "possible",
      "potential"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1962",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'houkoku'?",
    "Answer": "report"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1963",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toshi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "city",
      "town"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1964",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'politics'?",
    "Answer": "seiji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1965",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'competition'?",
    "Answer": "kyousou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1966",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cause'?",
    "Answer": "genin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1967",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'katsudou'?",
    "Answer": "activity"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1968",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'history'?",
    "Answer": "rekishi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1969",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "table",
      "list"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1970",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'website'?",
    "Answer": "saito"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1971",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'souvenir (plain)'?",
    "Answer": "miyage"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1972",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nioi'?",
    "Answer": "(bad) smell"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1973",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cash'?",
    "Answer": "genkin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1974",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'insect'?",
    "Answer": "mushi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1975",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stop by'?",
    "Answer": "yoru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1976",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'inaka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hometown",
      "countryside"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1977",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'return home'?",
    "Answer": "kitaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1978",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'juudai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "important",
      "serious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1979",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'minus'?",
    "Answer": "mainasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1980",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kasegu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "earn",
      "make money"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1981",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sayuu'?",
    "Answer": "right and left"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1982",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itami'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pain",
      "ache"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1983",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'misunderstanding'?",
    "Answer": "gokai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1984",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'complaint'?",
    "Answer": "monku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1985",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Europe and America'?",
    "Answer": "oubei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1986",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mensetsu'?",
    "Answer": "interview"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1987",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sain'?",
    "Answer": [
      "signature",
      "autograph"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1988",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nenjuu'?",
    "Answer": "all year"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1989",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mood'?",
    "Answer": "kigen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1990",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ima'?",
    "Answer": "living room"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1991",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'often'?",
    "Answer": "tabitabi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1992",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'example sentence'?",
    "Answer": "reibun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1993",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be lazy'?",
    "Answer": "namakeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1994",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tenkin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "change of job location",
      "relocation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1995",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seifu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "government",
      "administration"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1996",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shoyuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "ownership",
      "own"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1997",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'izure'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sometime later",
      "eventually"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1998",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taisuru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "face",
      "be in response to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q1999",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'church'?",
    "Answer": "kyoukai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2000",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'know (honorific)'?",
    "Answer": "gozonji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2001",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sparrow'?",
    "Answer": "suzume"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2002",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'proper'?",
    "Answer": "tekitou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2003",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rest'?",
    "Answer": "nokori"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2004",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'put (something) back'?",
    "Answer": "modosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2005",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'body weight'?",
    "Answer": "taijuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2006",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'anyway'?",
    "Answer": "douse"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2007",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'this and that'?",
    "Answer": "arekore"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2008",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mizuumi'?",
    "Answer": "lake"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2009",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toutou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "finally",
      "in the end"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2010",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'defeat'?",
    "Answer": "make"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2011",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'frustrating'?",
    "Answer": "kuyashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2012",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sisters'?",
    "Answer": "shimai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2013",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be helped'?",
    "Answer": "tasukaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2014",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'temae'?",
    "Answer": "in front"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2015",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'completely not'?",
    "Answer": "sappari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2016",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'on the way'?",
    "Answer": "tsuide"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2017",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'refreshed'?",
    "Answer": "sukkiri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2018",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tondemonai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "unthinkable",
      "outrageous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2019",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'saka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "slope",
      "hill"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2020",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tobikomu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "dive into",
      "jump into"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2021",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'comment'?",
    "Answer": "komento"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2022",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rewrite'?",
    "Answer": "kakinaosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2023",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kangofu'?",
    "Answer": "female nurse"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2024",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'finding a job'?",
    "Answer": "shuushoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2025",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'thread'?",
    "Answer": "ito"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2026",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sales floor'?",
    "Answer": "uriba"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2027",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'principal'?",
    "Answer": "kouchou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2028",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'field trip'?",
    "Answer": "kengaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2029",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shingaku'?",
    "Answer": "advance to higher education"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2030",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taiin'?",
    "Answer": "discharge from hospital"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2031",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tento'?",
    "Answer": "tent"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2032",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'odori'?",
    "Answer": [
      "dance",
      "dancing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2033",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ueru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "plant",
      "sow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2034",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'youchien'?",
    "Answer": "kindergarten"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2035",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'eameeru'?",
    "Answer": "airmail"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2036",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiki'?",
    "Answer": "the four seasons"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2037",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'nylon'?",
    "Answer": "nairon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2038",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fire engine'?",
    "Answer": "shoubousha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2039",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'handbag'?",
    "Answer": "handobaggu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2040",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'agriculture'?",
    "Answer": "nougyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2041",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'iron (for clothes)'?",
    "Answer": "airon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2042",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rasshuawaa'?",
    "Answer": "rush hour"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2043",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'special delivery'?",
    "Answer": "sokutatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2044",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yoshuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "preparation",
      "previewing (a lesson)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2045",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'registered mail'?",
    "Answer": "kakitome"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2046",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'depth'?",
    "Answer": "fukasa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2047",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'whisky'?",
    "Answer": "wisukii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2048",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mechanical pencil'?",
    "Answer": "shaapupenshiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2049",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'transaction'?",
    "Answer": "torihiki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2050",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'set up'?",
    "Answer": "moukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2051",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'fixed'?",
    "Answer": "ittei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2052",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kisha'?",
    "Answer": [
      "journalist",
      "reporter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2053",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'standard'?",
    "Answer": "kijun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2054",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tendency'?",
    "Answer": "keikou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2055",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'contract'?",
    "Answer": "keiyaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2056",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sangyou'?",
    "Answer": "industry"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2057",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jijou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "circumstances",
      "conditions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2058",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'practice'?",
    "Answer": "jikkou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2059",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'soshiki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "organization",
      "structure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2060",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'arrest'?",
    "Answer": "taiho"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2061",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'degree'?",
    "Answer": "teido"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2062",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'douyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "similar",
      "the same as"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2063",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'youkyuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "need",
      "demand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2064",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'boueki'?",
    "Answer": "(export and import) trade"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2065",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'export'?",
    "Answer": "yushutsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2066",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shougyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "commerce",
      "trade"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2067",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'surface mail'?",
    "Answer": "funabin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2068",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'election'?",
    "Answer": "senkyo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2069",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'juumin'?",
    "Answer": "resident"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2070",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'attendance'?",
    "Answer": "shusseki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2071",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'utterance'?",
    "Answer": "hatsugen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2072",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tomonau'?",
    "Answer": [
      "accompany",
      "entail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2073",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'employment'?",
    "Answer": "saiyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2074",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shori'?",
    "Answer": [
      "handling",
      "processing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2075",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'solution'?",
    "Answer": "kaiketsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2076",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the whole country'?",
    "Answer": "zenkoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2077",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'work'?",
    "Answer": "sagyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2078",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'production'?",
    "Answer": "seisan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2079",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'management'?",
    "Answer": "kanri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2080",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'increase'?",
    "Answer": "zouka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2081",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'distinctive feature'?",
    "Answer": "tokuchou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2082",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyouchou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "emphasis",
      "stress"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2083",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seido'?",
    "Answer": "system"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2084",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kabu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stock",
      "share"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2085",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kuwaeru'?",
    "Answer": "add (things of the same or different kinds)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2086",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyouka'?",
    "Answer": "strengthening"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2087",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sekkei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "design",
      "plan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2088",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dankai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stage",
      "phase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2089",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okonau'?",
    "Answer": [
      "do",
      "carry out"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2090",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'economy'?",
    "Answer": "keizai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2091",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koujou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "factory",
      "plant"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2092",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gijutsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "skill",
      "technology"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2093",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'facilities'?",
    "Answer": "shisetsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2094",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kami'?",
    "Answer": "God"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2095",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jinkou'?",
    "Answer": "population"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2096",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "party",
      "faction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2097",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yunyuu'?",
    "Answer": "import"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2098",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'simmer'?",
    "Answer": "niru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2099",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'konsaato'?",
    "Answer": "concert"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2100",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'gasoline'?",
    "Answer": "gasorin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2101",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pantsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pants",
      "trousers"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2102",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sokkuri'?",
    "Answer": "almost identical"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2103",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'meishi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "business card",
      "name card"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2104",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ichiichi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "every time",
      "about everything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2105",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'persistent'?",
    "Answer": "shitsukoi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2106",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nodo'?",
    "Answer": "throat"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2107",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shinchou'?",
    "Answer": "height"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2108",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nande'?",
    "Answer": [
      "why",
      "what for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2109",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'miso'?",
    "Answer": "soybean paste"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2110",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kinodoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pitiful",
      "poor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2111",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'softly'?",
    "Answer": "sotto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2112",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kossori'?",
    "Answer": "secretly"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2113",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ukkari'?",
    "Answer": [
      "carelessly",
      "accidentally"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2114",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wazato'?",
    "Answer": "on purpose"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2115",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gakkari'?",
    "Answer": [
      "disappointed",
      "disappointing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2116",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'vacantly'?",
    "Answer": "bonyari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2117",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'vinegar'?",
    "Answer": "su"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2118",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'urayamashii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "envious",
      "jealous"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2119",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsukamaeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "catch",
      "arrest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2120",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'not at all'?",
    "Answer": "chittomo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2121",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'thumb'?",
    "Answer": "oyayubi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2122",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'go past'?",
    "Answer": "toorisugiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2123",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'okujou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "housetop",
      "rooftop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2124",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lid'?",
    "Answer": "futa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2125",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itsunomanika'?",
    "Answer": [
      "before noticing it",
      "out of nowhere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2126",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'elephant'?",
    "Answer": "zou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2127",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iyagaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "dislike",
      "be unwilling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2128",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wagamama'?",
    "Answer": "selfish"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2129",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tetsuya'?",
    "Answer": "staying up all night"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2130",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'now now'?",
    "Answer": "maamaa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2131",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fuzakeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "mess around",
      "fool around"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2132",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ichidoni'?",
    "Answer": [
      "all at once",
      "at a time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2133",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'unazuku'?",
    "Answer": "nod"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2134",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ticket gate'?",
    "Answer": "kaisatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2135",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tetsudai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "help",
      "assistance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2136",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tokkuni'?",
    "Answer": [
      "long ago",
      "already"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2137",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'senzai'?",
    "Answer": "detergent"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2138",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wrist'?",
    "Answer": "tekubi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2139",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'a day trip'?",
    "Answer": "higaeri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2140",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cancel'?",
    "Answer": "torikesu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2141",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be amazed at'?",
    "Answer": "akireru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2142",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'getsumatsu'?",
    "Answer": "end of the month"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2143",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cough'?",
    "Answer": "seki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2144",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'unfortunately'?",
    "Answer": "ainiku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2145",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'go near'?",
    "Answer": "chikayoru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2146",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'in a loafing-about manner'?",
    "Answer": "urouro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2147",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'heavy'?",
    "Answer": "omotai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2148",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kajiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "nibble",
      "bite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2149",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be prolonged'?",
    "Answer": "nagabiku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2150",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sesseto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "diligently",
      "hard"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2151",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yokogiru'?",
    "Answer": "cut across"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2152",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'change'?",
    "Answer": "torikaeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2153",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'karakau'?",
    "Answer": [
      "make fun of",
      "tease"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2154",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sukikirai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "likes and dislikes",
      "taste"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2155",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mushiatsui'?",
    "Answer": "hot and humid"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2156",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shitaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "preparation",
      "getting ready"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2157",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'usugurai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "gloomy",
      "dim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2158",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kigae'?",
    "Answer": "change of clothes"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2159",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'one-piece dress'?",
    "Answer": "wanpiisu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2160",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seinengappi'?",
    "Answer": "year and date of birth"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2161",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mushiba'?",
    "Answer": "cavity"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2162",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'looking after the house'?",
    "Answer": "rusuban"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2163",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'harikiru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "go all out",
      "be full of energy (to do something)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2164",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ijiwaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "mean",
      "ill-natured"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2165",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'impudent'?",
    "Answer": "namaiki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2166",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiitsu'?",
    "Answer": "bed sheet"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2167",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'frying pan'?",
    "Answer": "furaipan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2168",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hitorihitori'?",
    "Answer": "each and every person"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2169",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'start a conversation'?",
    "Answer": "hanashikakeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2170",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'chase'?",
    "Answer": "oikakeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2171",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'little finger'?",
    "Answer": "koyubi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2172",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pikapika'?",
    "Answer": [
      "shiny",
      "glittering"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2173",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'middle finger'?",
    "Answer": "nakayubi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2174",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'eyelid'?",
    "Answer": "mabuta"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2175",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mendoukusai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "troublesome",
      "tiresome"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2176",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'boil'?",
    "Answer": "yuderu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2177",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dekirudake'?",
    "Answer": "as (much) as possible"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2178",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'moshikashitara'?",
    "Answer": [
      "possibly",
      "perhaps"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2179",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itsumademo'?",
    "Answer": "forever"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2180",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mabushii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "dazzling",
      "glaring"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2181",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oyatsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "snack",
      "refreshment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2182",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'empty'?",
    "Answer": "karappo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2183",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'butsubutsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "in a mutter",
      "mumble"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2184",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(feel) refreshed'?",
    "Answer": "sutto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2185",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'impudent'?",
    "Answer": "zuuzuushii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2186",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nikkori'?",
    "Answer": "smiling brightly"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2187",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stingy'?",
    "Answer": "kechi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2188",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oitsuku'?",
    "Answer": "catch up with"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2189",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sneeze'?",
    "Answer": "kushami"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2190",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'samasu'?",
    "Answer": "let cool"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2191",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'darashinai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "untidy",
      "sloppy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2192",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be indulgent to'?",
    "Answer": "amayakasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2193",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'irritated'?",
    "Answer": "iraira"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2194",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kusuriyubi'?",
    "Answer": "ring finger"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2195",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'slowly'?",
    "Answer": "noronoro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2196",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'point'?",
    "Answer": "pointo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2197",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kougyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "industry",
      "the manufacturing industry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2198",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'construction'?",
    "Answer": "kouzou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2199",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'just as expected'?",
    "Answer": "sasuga"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2200",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'doze'?",
    "Answer": "inemuri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2201",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chirakasu'?",
    "Answer": "make a mess"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2202",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get (something) wet'?",
    "Answer": "nurasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2203",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'date (fixed for something)'?",
    "Answer": "hinichi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2204",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ijimeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bully",
      "abuse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2205",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ashimoto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "step",
      "under foot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2206",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rabbit'?",
    "Answer": "usagi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2207",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kon'?",
    "Answer": [
      "dark blue",
      "navy blue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2208",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'in a mess'?",
    "Answer": "mechakucha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2209",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'no trespassing'?",
    "Answer": "tachiirikinshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2210",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'soon'?",
    "Answer": "mamonaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2211",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuuchou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bankbook",
      "passbook"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2212",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shibireru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "go numb",
      "fall asleep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2213",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gisshiri'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tightly",
      "closely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2214",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'gargling'?",
    "Answer": "ugai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2215",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'think of'?",
    "Answer": "omoitsuku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2216",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atena'?",
    "Answer": [
      "name of recipient",
      "addressee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2217",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cupboard'?",
    "Answer": "todana"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2218",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kogeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be burned",
      "be scorched"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2219",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'scratch'?",
    "Answer": "kaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2220",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ibaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be arrogant",
      "be boastful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2221",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'crowd'?",
    "Answer": "hitogomi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2222",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zurari'?",
    "Answer": "lining up neatly"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2223",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'to oneâ€™s heartâ€™s content'?",
    "Answer": "omoikiri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2224",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'aojiroi'?",
    "Answer": "pale"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2225",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shagamu'?",
    "Answer": "squat down"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2226",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kotobadukai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "wording",
      "language"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2227",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'happen to pass by'?",
    "Answer": "toorikakaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2228",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be out of touch'?",
    "Answer": "gobusata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2229",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shijou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "market (industrial",
      "financial",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2230",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'deeta'?",
    "Answer": "data"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2231",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'purchase'?",
    "Answer": "kounyuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2232",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'business'?",
    "Answer": "bijinesu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2233",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'I (masculine sense)'?",
    "Answer": "ore"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2234",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'touroku'?",
    "Answer": "registration"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2235",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taiken'?",
    "Answer": "personal experience"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2236",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'design'?",
    "Answer": "dezain"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2237",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'burden'?",
    "Answer": "futan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2238",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'details'?",
    "Answer": "shousai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2239",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'close-up'?",
    "Answer": "appu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2240",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'end'?",
    "Answer": "shuuryou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2241",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fan",
      "admirer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2242",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yosou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "expectation",
      "forecast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2243",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kikaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "planning",
      "project"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2244",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'public finance'?",
    "Answer": "zaisei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2245",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sougou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "integration",
      "put together"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2246",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'case'?",
    "Answer": "keesu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2247",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'maker'?",
    "Answer": "meekaa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2248",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'medical treatment'?",
    "Answer": "chiryou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2249",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dokusha'?",
    "Answer": "reader"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2250",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shokuin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "staff",
      "employee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2251",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'generation'?",
    "Answer": "sedai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2252",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'viewpoint'?",
    "Answer": "shiten"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2253",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'efficiency'?",
    "Answer": "kouritsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2254",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'property'?",
    "Answer": "shisan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2255",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'work on'?",
    "Answer": "torikumu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2256",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rule'?",
    "Answer": "ruuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2257",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shikaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "qualifications",
      "competence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2258",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'result'?",
    "Answer": "seika"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2259",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'assumption'?",
    "Answer": "zentei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2260",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'genchi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "local",
      "on-site"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2261",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'interior'?",
    "Answer": "naibu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2262",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'income'?",
    "Answer": "shotoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2263",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'romance'?",
    "Answer": "renai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2264",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'support'?",
    "Answer": "shiji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2265",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'crisis'?",
    "Answer": "kiki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2266",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mass media'?",
    "Answer": "masukomi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2267",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shouko'?",
    "Answer": [
      "proof",
      "evidence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2268",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koonaa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "section (of a store etc.)",
      "corner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2269",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'logo'?",
    "Answer": "maaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2270",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'decrease'?",
    "Answer": "genshou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2271",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kinkyuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "urgent",
      "emergency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2272",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'demand'?",
    "Answer": "youbou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2273",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sutoresu'?",
    "Answer": "stress"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2274",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sponsorship'?",
    "Answer": "shusai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2275",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'best'?",
    "Answer": "besuto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2276",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sacrifice'?",
    "Answer": "gisei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2277",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'violence'?",
    "Answer": "bouryoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2278",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'deficit'?",
    "Answer": "akaji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2279",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'individuality'?",
    "Answer": "kosei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2280",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakusen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tactic",
      "strategy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2281",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shock'?",
    "Answer": "shokku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2282",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'questionnaire'?",
    "Answer": "ankeeto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2283",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wazawaza'?",
    "Answer": "going out of oneâ€™s way to do something"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2284",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'serious'?",
    "Answer": "honki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2285",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'troubles'?",
    "Answer": "nayami"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2286",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'joushi'?",
    "Answer": "boss"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2287",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'persuasion'?",
    "Answer": "settoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2288",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'buumu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fad",
      "boom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2289",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'physical strength'?",
    "Answer": "tairyoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2290",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'normal'?",
    "Answer": "seijou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2291",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hint'?",
    "Answer": "hinto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2292",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hell'?",
    "Answer": "jigoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2293",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'regret'?",
    "Answer": "koukai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2294",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'passion'?",
    "Answer": "jounetsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2295",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'odoroki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "surprise",
      "amazement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2296",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'janpu'?",
    "Answer": "jump"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2297",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'arukooru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "alcohol",
      "alcoholic beverage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2298",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'irresponsible'?",
    "Answer": "iikagen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2299",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'feel excited'?",
    "Answer": "wakuwaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2300",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iiwake'?",
    "Answer": "excuse"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2301",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'music'?",
    "Answer": "myuujikku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2302",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'blossom of youth'?",
    "Answer": "seishun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2303",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'assari'?",
    "Answer": [
      "bluntly",
      "easily"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2304",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'feel pressured'?",
    "Answer": "aseru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2305",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pliable'?",
    "Answer": "juunan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2306",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'celebrity'?",
    "Answer": "tarento"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2307",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dounika'?",
    "Answer": "somehow"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2308",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kontesuto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "contest",
      "competition"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2309",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be popular (esp. with the opposite sex)'?",
    "Answer": "moteru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2310",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'dessert'?",
    "Answer": "dezaato"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2311",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'quiz'?",
    "Answer": "kuizu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2312",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'poisoning'?",
    "Answer": "chuudoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2313",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'muudo'?",
    "Answer": "mood"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2314",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sympathy'?",
    "Answer": "doujou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2315",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gakureki'?",
    "Answer": "educational background"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2316",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'good condition'?",
    "Answer": "kouchou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2317",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'amateur'?",
    "Answer": "amachua"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2318",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itameru'?",
    "Answer": "stir-fry"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2319",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'photographer'?",
    "Answer": "kameraman"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2320",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toiawaseru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "inquire",
      "ask for (information)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2321",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'frequently'?",
    "Answer": "shocchuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2322",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'roopu'?",
    "Answer": "rope"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2323",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sutoraiki'?",
    "Answer": "strike"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2324",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'panku'?",
    "Answer": "flat tire"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2325",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'komaasharu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "commercial",
      "advertising"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2326",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'change'?",
    "Answer": "chenji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2327",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'machiawase'?",
    "Answer": [
      "meeting with someone",
      "appointment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2328",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jisa'?",
    "Answer": "time difference"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2329",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sense of duty'?",
    "Answer": "giri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2330",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'quickly'?",
    "Answer": "satto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2331",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hidarikiki'?",
    "Answer": "left-handedness"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2332",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'saboru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "slack of",
      "ditch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2333",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'darui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "feel run-down",
      "weary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2334",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'potto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "pot",
      "thermos"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2335",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'X-rays'?",
    "Answer": "rentogen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2336",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kokoroduyoi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "reassuring",
      "heartening"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2337",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mudadukai'?",
    "Answer": "wasteful spending"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2338",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bajji'?",
    "Answer": "badge"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2339",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ophthalmology'?",
    "Answer": "ganka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2340",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rirekisho'?",
    "Answer": [
      "resume",
      "curriculum vitae"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2341",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'inflation'?",
    "Answer": "infureeshon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2342",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cancer'?",
    "Answer": "gan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2343",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bow'?",
    "Answer": "pekopeko"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2344",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'usotsuki'?",
    "Answer": "liar"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2345",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ogoru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "treat",
      "pay for (someone)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2346",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'juujiro'?",
    "Answer": "crossroads"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2347",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bisshori'?",
    "Answer": [
      "drenched",
      "soaked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2348",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'baggy'?",
    "Answer": "dabudabu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2349",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'flatter'?",
    "Answer": "odateru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2350",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kakato'?",
    "Answer": "heel"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2351",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'feel relieved'?",
    "Answer": "hotto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2352",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hurt (someone)'?",
    "Answer": "kizutsukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2353",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'look down'?",
    "Answer": "utsumuku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2354",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maeuriken'?",
    "Answer": "advance ticket"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2355",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tanki'?",
    "Answer": "short-term"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2356",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nameru'?",
    "Answer": "lick"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2357",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'today (formal)'?",
    "Answer": "honjitsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2358",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'industry'?",
    "Answer": "gyoukai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2359",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nettowaaku'?",
    "Answer": "network"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2360",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lawyer'?",
    "Answer": "bengoshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2361",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'input'?",
    "Answer": "nyuuryoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2362",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zenkai'?",
    "Answer": "last time"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2363",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gamen'?",
    "Answer": "screen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2364",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'latter half'?",
    "Answer": "kouhan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2365",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jishin'?",
    "Answer": "confidence"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2366",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lovely'?",
    "Answer": "suteki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2367",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'no wonder'?",
    "Answer": "atarimae"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2368",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'way of doing'?",
    "Answer": "yarikata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2369",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wazuka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "meager",
      "marginal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2370",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'at last'?",
    "Answer": "tsuini"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2371",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'next time'?",
    "Answer": "jikai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2372",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'speed'?",
    "Answer": "supiido"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2373",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'baito'?",
    "Answer": "part-time job"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2374",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'impossible'?",
    "Answer": "fukanou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2375",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'advice'?",
    "Answer": "adobaisu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2376",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'calm down'?",
    "Answer": "ochitsuku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2377",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sekkaku'?",
    "Answer": "with much trouble"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2378",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "inadvertently",
      "carelessly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2379",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oote'?",
    "Answer": "major company"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2380",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'buchou'?",
    "Answer": "department head"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2381",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zenhan'?",
    "Answer": "first half"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2382",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'by chance'?",
    "Answer": "tamatama"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2383",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'as usual'?",
    "Answer": "aikawarazu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2384",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiharai'?",
    "Answer": "payment"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2385",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'number of people'?",
    "Answer": "ninzuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2386",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kachou'?",
    "Answer": "section chief"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2387",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fasshon'?",
    "Answer": "fashion"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2388",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taichou'?",
    "Answer": "health condition"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2389",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'socialize with'?",
    "Answer": "tsukiau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2390",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shoppingu'?",
    "Answer": "shopping"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2391",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ant'?",
    "Answer": "ari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2392",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'worst'?",
    "Answer": "saiaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2393",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'frog'?",
    "Answer": "kaeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2394",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Mister'?",
    "Answer": "ojisan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2395",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "advantage",
      "gain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2396",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'grip'?",
    "Answer": "tsukamu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2397",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiriai'?",
    "Answer": "acquaintance"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2398",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'peesu'?",
    "Answer": "pace"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2399",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'to produce'?",
    "Answer": "sakusei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2400",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'parent and child'?",
    "Answer": "oyako"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2401",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'talk'?",
    "Answer": "hanashiai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2402",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'head office of a company'?",
    "Answer": "honsha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2403",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'meeting'?",
    "Answer": "uchiawase"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2404",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mimamoru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "watch",
      "keep watch over"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2405",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'uriage'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sales",
      "proceeds"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2406",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaette'?",
    "Answer": [
      "rather",
      "instead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2407",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'aidoru'?",
    "Answer": "idol"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2408",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nantonaku'?",
    "Answer": "for some reason"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2409",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'end of year'?",
    "Answer": "nenmatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2410",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'muishiki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "unconsciously",
      "unintentionally"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2411",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'in front of the station'?",
    "Answer": "ekimae"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2412",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'come all the way'?",
    "Answer": "yattekuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2413",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kicchin'?",
    "Answer": "kitchen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2414",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'kiss'?",
    "Answer": "kisu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2415",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'awateru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be flustered",
      "be in a hurry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2416",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'in the metropolitan area of Tokyo'?",
    "Answer": "tonai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2417",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zangyou'?",
    "Answer": "overtime work"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2418",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'aimai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "ambiguous",
      "vague"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2419",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'katarogu'?",
    "Answer": "catalogue"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2420",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hit'?",
    "Answer": "naguru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2421",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'both hands'?",
    "Answer": "ryoute"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2422",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nakayoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "harmoniously",
      "getting along"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2423",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'beginning'?",
    "Answer": "hajime"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2424",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get acquainted with'?",
    "Answer": "shiriau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2425",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'otetsudai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "help",
      "assistance (polite)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2426",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'manaa'?",
    "Answer": "manners"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2427",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'karaoke'?",
    "Answer": "karaoke"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2428",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nidoto'?",
    "Answer": "never again"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2429",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'one hand'?",
    "Answer": "katate"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2430",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'middle-aged woman'?",
    "Answer": "obasan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2431",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hoikuen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "day-care center",
      "nursery school"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2432",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zureru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "go off track",
      "go out of line"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2433",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'beach'?",
    "Answer": "biichi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2434",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seizei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "at most",
      "at best"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2435",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kouki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "latter term",
      "second half"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2436",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'eakon'?",
    "Answer": [
      "air-conditioning",
      "air conditioner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2437",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'comfortable'?",
    "Answer": "yuttari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2438",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'haadowea'?",
    "Answer": "hardware"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2439",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'request'?",
    "Answer": "rikuesuto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2440",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the following year'?",
    "Answer": "yokunen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2441",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cancellation'?",
    "Answer": "kyanseru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2442",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shanai'?",
    "Answer": "inside a vehicle or a train"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2443",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'loud voice'?",
    "Answer": "oogoe"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2444",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'musekinin'?",
    "Answer": "irresponsible"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2445",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'katahou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "one side",
      "the other one"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2446",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'volume'?",
    "Answer": "boryuumu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2447",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zenpou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "front",
      "ahead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2448",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nihonshu'?",
    "Answer": "Japanese rice wine"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2449",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'aozora'?",
    "Answer": "blue sky"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2450",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'unnatural'?",
    "Answer": "fushizen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2451",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'last night'?",
    "Answer": "sakuban"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2452",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiyakusho'?",
    "Answer": [
      "municipal office",
      "city hall"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2453",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'furuutsu'?",
    "Answer": "fruit"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2454",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'year by year'?",
    "Answer": "nennen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2455",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kouhou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "back",
      "rear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2456",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'apologize'?",
    "Answer": "owabi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2457",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'oriental radish'?",
    "Answer": "daikon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2458",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'peel (something)'?",
    "Answer": "muku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2459",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'typical year'?",
    "Answer": "reinen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2460",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'deadline'?",
    "Answer": "shimekiri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2461",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'masani'?",
    "Answer": [
      "just",
      "surely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2462",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'snake'?",
    "Answer": "hebi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2463",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rasshu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "rush",
      "rush hour"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2464",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oogesa'?",
    "Answer": "exaggerated"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2465",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'forcibly'?",
    "Answer": "muriyari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2466",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gaishoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "eating out",
      "dining out"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2467",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cabbage'?",
    "Answer": "kyabetsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2468",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hands and feet'?",
    "Answer": "teashi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2469",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shop closing'?",
    "Answer": "heiten"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2470",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'department store'?",
    "Answer": "hyakkaten"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2471",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cookie'?",
    "Answer": "kukkii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2472",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'wheelchair'?",
    "Answer": "kurumaisu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2473",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ooame'?",
    "Answer": "heavy rain"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2474",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pigeon'?",
    "Answer": "hato"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2475",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'middle-class'?",
    "Answer": "chuukyuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2476",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'onigiri'?",
    "Answer": "rice ball"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2477",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'perhaps'?",
    "Answer": "hyottoshitara"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2478",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'round and round'?",
    "Answer": "guruguru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2479",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'washoku'?",
    "Answer": "Japanese-style food"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2480",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'doku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "get out of the way",
      "step aside"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2481",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'uesuto'?",
    "Answer": "waist"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2482",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bounenkai'?",
    "Answer": "year-end party"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2483",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'houchou'?",
    "Answer": "kitchen knife"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2484",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'golden week'?",
    "Answer": "goorudenwiiku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2485",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shoes'?",
    "Answer": "shuuzu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2486",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'minor'?",
    "Answer": "miseinen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2487",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oi'?",
    "Answer": "nephew"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2488",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'leaf'?",
    "Answer": "happa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2489",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'do over again'?",
    "Answer": "yarinaosu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2490",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oomisoka'?",
    "Answer": "new yearâ€™s eve"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2491",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sunglasses'?",
    "Answer": "sangurasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2492",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'byounin'?",
    "Answer": "sick person"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2493",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaoiro'?",
    "Answer": [
      "complexion",
      "facial expression"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2494",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'golden color'?",
    "Answer": "kiniro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2495",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'glare'?",
    "Answer": "niramu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2496",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsukamaru'?",
    "Answer": "hold on to (something)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2497",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ankle'?",
    "Answer": "ashikubi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2498",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'be in a mess'?",
    "Answer": "chirakaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2499",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get nervous'?",
    "Answer": "agaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2500",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pumpkin'?",
    "Answer": "kabocha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2501",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'aquarium'?",
    "Answer": "suizokukan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2502",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sold out'?",
    "Answer": "shinagire"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2503",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'swell up'?",
    "Answer": "hareru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2504",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yarinaoshi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "doing over",
      "redoing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2505",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bargain sale'?",
    "Answer": "baagen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2506",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'otokorashii'?",
    "Answer": [
      "manly",
      "masculine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2507",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chikamichi'?",
    "Answer": "shortcut"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2508",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'toast'?",
    "Answer": "toosuto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2509",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'curiosity'?",
    "Answer": "koukishin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2510",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'practical'?",
    "Answer": "jitsuyouteki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2511",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyakkanteki'?",
    "Answer": "objective"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2512",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'abstract'?",
    "Answer": "chuushouteki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2513",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'farewell party'?",
    "Answer": "soubetsukai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2514",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'deposit'?",
    "Answer": "shikikin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2515",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nichibei'?",
    "Answer": "Japan and the US"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2516",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'specialist'?",
    "Answer": "senmonka"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2517",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hot'?",
    "Answer": "hotto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2518",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wasabi'?",
    "Answer": "Japanese horseradish"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2519",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hatsumoude'?",
    "Answer": "first shrine visit of the new year"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2520",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jogingu'?",
    "Answer": "jogging"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2521",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shakaijin'?",
    "Answer": "working member of society"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2522",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'in a great hurry'?",
    "Answer": "ooisogi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2523",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'self-service'?",
    "Answer": "serufusaabisu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2524",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'messy'?",
    "Answer": "kushakusha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2525",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'bread in a rectangular shape'?",
    "Answer": "shokupan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2526",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hitosashiyubi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "index finger",
      "forefinger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2527",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'youshoku'?",
    "Answer": "Western food"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2528",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'damp'?",
    "Answer": "jimejime"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2529",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'staringly'?",
    "Answer": "jirojiro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2530",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'smooth'?",
    "Answer": "tsurutsuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2531",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pepper'?",
    "Answer": "koshou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2532",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bishobisho'?",
    "Answer": [
      "soaking wet",
      "soaked"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2533",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'packed'?",
    "Answer": "gyuugyuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2534",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'batsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "cross",
      "x-mark (on errors",
      "mistakes etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2535",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'light blue'?",
    "Answer": "mizuiro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2536",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ryoushuusho'?",
    "Answer": "bill of receipt (for payment only)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2537",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shizenni'?",
    "Answer": "naturally"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2538",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pork cutlet'?",
    "Answer": "tonkatsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2539",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'spring onion'?",
    "Answer": "negi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2540",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyuuri'?",
    "Answer": "cucumber"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2541",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'unagi'?",
    "Answer": "eel"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2542",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'maguro'?",
    "Answer": "tuna"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2543",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'painappuru'?",
    "Answer": "pineapple"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2544",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'spinach'?",
    "Answer": "hourensou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2545",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mayonnaise'?",
    "Answer": "mayoneezu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2546",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tamanegi'?",
    "Answer": "onion"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2547",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yakiniku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "grilled meat",
      "barbecued meat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2548",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'eye drops'?",
    "Answer": "megusuri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2549",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nesugosu'?",
    "Answer": "oversleep"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2550",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kokusaiteki'?",
    "Answer": "international"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2551",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'internationalization'?",
    "Answer": "kokusaika"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2552",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ward office'?",
    "Answer": "kuyakusho"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2553",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'washitsu'?",
    "Answer": "Japanese-style room"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2554",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'honkakuteki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "authentic",
      "serious"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2555",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kousokudouro'?",
    "Answer": [
      "freeway",
      "expressway"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2556",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toriaezu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "for now",
      "for the time being"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2557",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakini'?",
    "Answer": [
      "before",
      "ahead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2558",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'girigiri'?",
    "Answer": [
      "just in time",
      "barely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2559",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'awatadashii'?",
    "Answer": "busy and hurried"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2560",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'imagoro'?",
    "Answer": [
      "by now",
      "at this time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2561",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stick'?",
    "Answer": "kuttsuku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2562",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kitakaze'?",
    "Answer": "north wind"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2563",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shrimp'?",
    "Answer": "ebi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2564",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'omoikitte'?",
    "Answer": [
      "daringly",
      "taking the plunge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2565",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'taken aback'?",
    "Answer": "hatto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2566",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'recipientâ€™s address'?",
    "Answer": "atesaki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2567",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'barabara'?",
    "Answer": [
      "separately",
      "discretely"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2568",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'train ticket'?",
    "Answer": "joushaken"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2569",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'shivering'?",
    "Answer": "buruburu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2570",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'surasura'?",
    "Answer": [
      "smoothly",
      "easily"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2571",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'last train'?",
    "Answer": "shuuden"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2572",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cunning'?",
    "Answer": "zurui"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2573",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(sleep) peacefully'?",
    "Answer": "suyasuya"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2574",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gatagata'?",
    "Answer": [
      "with a rattling noise",
      "unstable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2575",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hijouguchi'?",
    "Answer": "emergency exit"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2576",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'rough'?",
    "Answer": "zarazara"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2577",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nurunuru'?",
    "Answer": "slimy"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2578",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'womanly'?",
    "Answer": "onnarashii"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2579",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'urgent business'?",
    "Answer": "kyuuyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2580",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'look around'?",
    "Answer": "kyorokyoro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2581",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'slowly'?",
    "Answer": "guzuguzu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2582",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pokapoka'?",
    "Answer": "pleasantly warm"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2583",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'araimono'?",
    "Answer": "dishes to be washed"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2584",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'katto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "in a temper",
      "in a rage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2585",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'surprised'?",
    "Answer": "dokitto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2586",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'miss (a train'?",
    "Answer": "noriokureru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2587",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'exhausted'?",
    "Answer": "kutakuta"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2588",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'smooth'?",
    "Answer": "subesube"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2589",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'niyaniya'?",
    "Answer": "grin to oneself"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2590",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'adana'?",
    "Answer": "nickname"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2591",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atokataduke'?",
    "Answer": "cleaning up"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2592",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ika'?",
    "Answer": "squid"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2593",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ukiuki'?",
    "Answer": "excitedly"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2594",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kawaigaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "love",
      "cherish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2595",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Chinese dumpling'?",
    "Answer": "gyouza"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2596",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'geragera'?",
    "Answer": "(laugh) out loud"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2597",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gomen'?",
    "Answer": "sorry"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2598",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiasatte'?",
    "Answer": "three days from today"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2599",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakugen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "cutdown",
      "reduction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2600",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zeitaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "luxury",
      "extravagance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2601",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'before long'?",
    "Answer": "sonouchi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2602",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dekoboko'?",
    "Answer": [
      "unevenness",
      "bumpiness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2603",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'palm'?",
    "Answer": "tenohira"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2604",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hadashi'?",
    "Answer": "bare feet"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2605",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'betabeta'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stick together",
      "sticky"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2606",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mayuge'?",
    "Answer": "eyebrows"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2607",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'disposable chopsticks'?",
    "Answer": "waribashi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2608",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hiduke'?",
    "Answer": [
      "date (written in a document",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2609",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'pitarito'?",
    "Answer": [
      "suddenly",
      "coming to a dead stop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2610",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'manaita'?",
    "Answer": "chopping board"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2611",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'pens and pencils'?",
    "Answer": "hikkiyougu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2612",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kusuguru'?",
    "Answer": "tickle"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2613",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kankan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "furiously angry",
      "in a rage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2614",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hakusen'?",
    "Answer": "white (warning) line"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2615",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'recognition'?",
    "Answer": "mioboe"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2616",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'until now'?",
    "Answer": "koremade"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2617",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'karasu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "crow",
      "raven"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2618",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kamitsuku'?",
    "Answer": "bite"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2619",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Chinese cabbage'?",
    "Answer": "hakusai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2620",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'puroyakyuu'?",
    "Answer": "professional baseball"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2621",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kamisori'?",
    "Answer": "razor"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2622",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nanjuu'?",
    "Answer": "several tens"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2623",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'several hundred'?",
    "Answer": "nanbyaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2624",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'several thousand'?",
    "Answer": "nanzen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2625",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sharply'?",
    "Answer": "gakunto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2626",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tobioriru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "jump off",
      "jump down"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2627",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'road closed'?",
    "Answer": "tsuukoudome"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2628",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ikidomari'?",
    "Answer": "dead end"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2629",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'perfect circle'?",
    "Answer": "manmaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2630",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'itsunomani'?",
    "Answer": "without anyone noticing"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2631",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'attach (something)'?",
    "Answer": "kuttsukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2632",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'add on'?",
    "Answer": "tsuketasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2633",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tokusuru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "profitable",
      "beneficial"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2634",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lose'?",
    "Answer": "sonsuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2635",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'iikaesu'?",
    "Answer": "talk back"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2636",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taionkei'?",
    "Answer": "(clinical) thermometer"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2637",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'atomodori'?",
    "Answer": [
      "turning back",
      "retreat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2638",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hanashigoe'?",
    "Answer": "talking voice"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2639",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'round and round'?",
    "Answer": "kurukuru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2640",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kowagaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be afraid of",
      "fear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2641",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hitochigai'?",
    "Answer": "mistaken identity"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2642",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'torikaesu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "take back",
      "regain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2643",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'noriori'?",
    "Answer": "getting on and off"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2644",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kuchigenka'?",
    "Answer": "quarrel"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2645",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'get up'?",
    "Answer": "okiagaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2646",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'burasagaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hang down",
      "dangle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2647",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tobiagaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "fly up",
      "fump up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2648",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nakigoe'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tearful voice",
      "sound of crying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2649",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mochimono'?",
    "Answer": "oneâ€™s belongings"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2650",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'long and thin'?",
    "Answer": "hosonagai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2651",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'doorway'?",
    "Answer": "deiriguchi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2652",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seiza'?",
    "Answer": "sitting on oneâ€™s heels"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2653",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ooyorokobi'?",
    "Answer": "great joy"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2654",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lost property'?",
    "Answer": "otoshimono"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2655",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'janjan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "many times",
      "repeatedly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2656",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'michigaeru'?",
    "Answer": "look completely different"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2657",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gouriteki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "rational",
      "logical"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2658",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'voluntary'?",
    "Answer": "jishuteki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2659",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zenmenteki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "full-scale",
      "complete"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2660",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'endaka'?",
    "Answer": "strong yen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2661",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'consumer'?",
    "Answer": "shouhisha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2662",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'Japan and China'?",
    "Answer": "nicchuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2663",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'asu'?",
    "Answer": "tomorrow (rather formal)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2664",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kekkou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "all right",
      "no thank you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2665",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'hard'?",
    "Answer": "tsurai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2666",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mazui'?",
    "Answer": [
      "problematic",
      "troublesome"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2667",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'top and bottom'?",
    "Answer": "jouge"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2668",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'raw'?",
    "Answer": "nama"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2669",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yokeru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "avoid",
      "dodge"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2670",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gayagaya'?",
    "Answer": [
      "noisily",
      "loudly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2671",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'akanbou'?",
    "Answer": "(human) baby"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2672",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'word processor'?",
    "Answer": "waapuro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2673",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shinbunsha'?",
    "Answer": "newspaper publisher"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2674",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nekasu'?",
    "Answer": "put (someone) to bed"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2675",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'person (humble)'?",
    "Answer": "mono"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2676",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "middle",
      "medium size"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2677",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'gender'?",
    "Answer": "sei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2678",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'meeting'?",
    "Answer": "kai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2679",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'thing'?",
    "Answer": "koto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2680",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'these days'?",
    "Answer": "konnichi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2681",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ten'?",
    "Answer": [
      "point (of concern)",
      "dot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2682",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'back'?",
    "Answer": "bakku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2683",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kiji'?",
    "Answer": [
      "article",
      "story"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2684",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "big",
      "large size"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2685",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "law",
      "rule"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2686",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hijou'?",
    "Answer": "emergency"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2687",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'simply'?",
    "Answer": "tada"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2688",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'feeling'?",
    "Answer": "kanji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2689",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'environment'?",
    "Answer": "kankyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2690",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rikai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "understanding",
      "comprehension"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2691",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ken'?",
    "Answer": "prefecture"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2692",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiyou'?",
    "Answer": "use"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2693",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shugi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "principle",
      "-ism"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2694",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kokumin'?",
    "Answer": "citizen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2695",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'under (someoneâ€™s) supervision'?",
    "Answer": "moto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2696",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ba'?",
    "Answer": [
      "occasion",
      "situation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2697",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'roudou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "labor",
      "work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2698",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kikai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "opportunity",
      "chance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2699",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seihin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "product",
      "manufactured goods"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2700",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'self'?",
    "Answer": "jishin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2701",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'catch (a cold'?",
    "Answer": "kakaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2702",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'seek'?",
    "Answer": "motomeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2703",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kudasaru'?",
    "Answer": "give (honorific)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2704",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sakujitsu'?",
    "Answer": "yesterday (formal)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2705",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'moto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "origin",
      "former"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2706",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kata'?",
    "Answer": [
      "type",
      "model"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2707",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sorezore'?",
    "Answer": [
      "each",
      "respectively"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2708",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chihou'?",
    "Answer": "local region"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2709",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'surface'?",
    "Answer": "men"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2710",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jitsuha'?",
    "Answer": "actually"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2711",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yoru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "night",
      "evening"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2712",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ground'?",
    "Answer": "chi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2713",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'discussion'?",
    "Answer": "giron"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2714",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'before'?",
    "Answer": "izen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2715",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'specialty'?",
    "Answer": "senmon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2716",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'moushiageru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tell",
      "say (humble)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2717",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koudou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "action",
      "conduct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2718",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ratio'?",
    "Answer": "ritsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2719",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kantoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "supervisor",
      "film director"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2720",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'consciousness'?",
    "Answer": "ishiki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2721",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'recognize'?",
    "Answer": "mitomeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2722",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'reference'?",
    "Answer": "sankou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2723",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'team'?",
    "Answer": "chiimu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2724",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'reality'?",
    "Answer": "genjitsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2725",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'value'?",
    "Answer": "kachi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2726",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'teema'?",
    "Answer": [
      "theme",
      "subject matter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2727",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'contain'?",
    "Answer": "fukumu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2728",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "opportunity",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2729",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'subete'?",
    "Answer": [
      "all",
      "everything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2730",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'daijin'?",
    "Answer": "minister"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2731",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kokka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "state",
      "nation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2732",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shiai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "match",
      "game"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2733",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kekkyoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "after all",
      "finally"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2734",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shouhi'?",
    "Answer": [
      "consumption",
      "spending"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2735",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jinsei'?",
    "Answer": "oneâ€™s life (to lead)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2736",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ryou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "quantity",
      "amount"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2737",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mind'?",
    "Answer": "seishin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2738",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'reberu'?",
    "Answer": "level"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2739",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'wareware'?",
    "Answer": "we (literary)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2740",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shidou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "guide",
      "instruction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2741",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'myounichi'?",
    "Answer": "tomorrow (very formal)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2742",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'materials'?",
    "Answer": "shiryou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2743",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'group'?",
    "Answer": "dantai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2744",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mottomo'?",
    "Answer": "the most"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2745",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanzen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "perfect",
      "complete"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2746",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'goods'?",
    "Answer": "shina"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2747",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'male'?",
    "Answer": "dansei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2748",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gun'?",
    "Answer": "military"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2749",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'depict'?",
    "Answer": "egaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2750",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'final'?",
    "Answer": "saishuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2751",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sentaa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "center (for an activity",
      "etc.)",
      "hub"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2752",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'obstacle'?",
    "Answer": "shougai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2753",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'medical service'?",
    "Answer": "iryou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2754",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'receive'?",
    "Answer": "itadaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2755",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kinyuu'?",
    "Answer": "finance"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2756",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'learn'?",
    "Answer": "manabu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2757",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'growth'?",
    "Answer": "seichou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2758",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'toujou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "appearance (on stage",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2759",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chishiki'?",
    "Answer": "knowledge"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2760",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'friend (formal)'?",
    "Answer": "yuujin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2761",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'imeeji'?",
    "Answer": "image"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2762",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'top'?",
    "Answer": "toppu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2763",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tax'?",
    "Answer": "zei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2764",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'henkou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "alteration",
      "change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2765",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kagiri'?",
    "Answer": "limit"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2766",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'ceremony'?",
    "Answer": "shiki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2767",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'development'?",
    "Answer": "tenkai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2768",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyoumi'?",
    "Answer": "interest"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2769",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'fukumeru'?",
    "Answer": "include"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2770",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'editing'?",
    "Answer": "henshuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2771",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'selection'?",
    "Answer": "sentaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2772",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'muryou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "no charge",
      "free"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2773",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'body'?",
    "Answer": "mi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2774",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bunseki'?",
    "Answer": "analysis"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2775",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yosan'?",
    "Answer": "budget"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2776",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mokuhyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "target",
      "goal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2777",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuushin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "correspondence",
      "communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2778",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'turn toward'?",
    "Answer": "mukeru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2779",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'time (formal)'?",
    "Answer": "jikoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2780",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gyaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "reverse",
      "opposite"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2781",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'supreme'?",
    "Answer": "saikou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2782",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'rieki'?",
    "Answer": [
      "profit",
      "benefit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2783",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'jimu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "office work",
      "business"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2784",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shuppan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "publishing",
      "publication"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2785",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'professional'?",
    "Answer": "puro"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2786",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'samazama'?",
    "Answer": [
      "various",
      "diverse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2787",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'state'?",
    "Answer": "shuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2788",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kyoutsuu'?",
    "Answer": "commonality"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2789",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'present age'?",
    "Answer": "gendai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2790",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'higai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "damage",
      "harm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2791",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'new'?",
    "Answer": "arata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2792",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'suitability'?",
    "Answer": "soutou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2793",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'renewal'?",
    "Answer": "koushin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2794",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'obtain'?",
    "Answer": "eru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2795",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'inside'?",
    "Answer": "uchi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2796",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'maintenance'?",
    "Answer": "iji"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2797",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ryoukin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "charge",
      "fee (for using facilities",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2798",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'arrival'?",
    "Answer": "touchaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2799",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'namamono'?",
    "Answer": "uncooked food"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2800",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'chapter'?",
    "Answer": "shou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2801",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'menbaa'?",
    "Answer": "member"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2802",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ensou'?",
    "Answer": "musical performance"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2803",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'plan'?",
    "Answer": "an"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2804",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kibou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "hope",
      "wish"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2805",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kioku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "memory",
      "remembrance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2806",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'moderu'?",
    "Answer": "model"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2807",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'people (polite)'?",
    "Answer": "katagata"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2808",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'launch'?",
    "Answer": "hatsubai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2809",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'topic of conversation'?",
    "Answer": "wadai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2810",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'aim for'?",
    "Answer": "mezasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2811",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kenchiku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "construction",
      "architecture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2812",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'inshou'?",
    "Answer": "impression"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2813",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kenri'?",
    "Answer": [
      "right",
      "privilege"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2814",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gakushuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "study",
      "learning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2815",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'development'?",
    "Answer": "hatten"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2816",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'scene'?",
    "Answer": "genba"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2817",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'feeling'?",
    "Answer": "kibun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2818",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'movement'?",
    "Answer": "idou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2819",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'publication'?",
    "Answer": "hakkou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2820",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'religion'?",
    "Answer": "shuukyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2821",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'revision'?",
    "Answer": "kaisei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2822",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'bai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "double",
      "times"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2823",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'uneasy'?",
    "Answer": "fuan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2824",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for '(for) oneself'?",
    "Answer": "mizukara"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2825",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koukoku'?",
    "Answer": "advertisement"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2826",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'joint'?",
    "Answer": "kyoudou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2827",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'generation'?",
    "Answer": "nendai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2828",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taipu'?",
    "Answer": "type"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2829",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'difference'?",
    "Answer": "sa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2830",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'eigyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "business",
      "sales"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2831",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'role'?",
    "Answer": "yakuwari"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2832",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaizen'?",
    "Answer": "improvement"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2833",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'photographing'?",
    "Answer": "satsuei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2834",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'enerugii'?",
    "Answer": "energy"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2835",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'constitution'?",
    "Answer": "kenpou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2836",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'gratitude'?",
    "Answer": "kansha"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2837",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kankaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "sense",
      "feel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2838",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'journey'?",
    "Answer": "tabi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2839",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'awaseru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "match (something)",
      "adapt (oneself)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2840",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'already'?",
    "Answer": "sudeni"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2841",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'genjou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "current condition",
      "situation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2842",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'senjitsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "the other day",
      "a few days ago"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2843",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'center'?",
    "Answer": "chuuou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2844",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'niru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "resemble",
      "be alike"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2845",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'heikin'?",
    "Answer": "average"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2846",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the end'?",
    "Answer": "sue"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2847",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuika'?",
    "Answer": [
      "addition",
      "supplement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2848",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nasaru'?",
    "Answer": "do (honorific)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2849",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the state of affairs'?",
    "Answer": "yousu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2850",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'katsuyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "practical use",
      "application"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2851",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koukan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "exchange",
      "bartering"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2852",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seibi'?",
    "Answer": "maintenance"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2853",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'imagination'?",
    "Answer": "souzou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2854",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'like that'?",
    "Answer": "aa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2855",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'satisfaction'?",
    "Answer": "manzoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2856",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'thereafter'?",
    "Answer": "ikou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2857",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hikaku'?",
    "Answer": "comparison"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2858",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'class'?",
    "Answer": "kurasu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2859",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hanzai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "offense",
      "crime"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2860",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'say'?",
    "Answer": "ossharu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2861",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tokutei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "specifying",
      "identifying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2862",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kiso'?",
    "Answer": [
      "base",
      "foundation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2863",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nagare'?",
    "Answer": [
      "flow",
      "stream"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2864",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'for no special reason'?",
    "Answer": "doumo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2865",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mura'?",
    "Answer": "village"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2866",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'stability'?",
    "Answer": "antei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2867",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'the person himself'?",
    "Answer": "honnin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2868",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'atmosphere'?",
    "Answer": "funiki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2869",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'venue'?",
    "Answer": "kaijou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2870",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'electron'?",
    "Answer": "denshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2871",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'sentence'?",
    "Answer": "bun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2872",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'range'?",
    "Answer": "hani"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2873",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tsuneni'?",
    "Answer": [
      "always",
      "at all times (formal)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2874",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lose'?",
    "Answer": "ushinau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2875",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nichijou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "everyday life",
      "daily life"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2876",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kaitou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "reply",
      "answer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2877",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'taisei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "system",
      "structure"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2878",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chousei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "regulation",
      "adjustment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2879",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'question'?",
    "Answer": "gimon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2880",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ouen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "support",
      "cheering"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2881",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kansou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "thought",
      "impression"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2882",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'explanation'?",
    "Answer": "kaisetsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2883",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'series'?",
    "Answer": "shiriizu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2884",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koukyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "public",
      "community"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2885",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'minkan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "private",
      "civilian"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2886",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'saiban'?",
    "Answer": [
      "trial",
      "judgment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2887",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'union'?",
    "Answer": "kumiai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2888",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'honrai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "originally",
      "primarily"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2889",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'what on earth'?",
    "Answer": "ittai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2890",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'uchuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "universe",
      "space"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2891",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'mousu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "say",
      "tell (humble)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2892",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "figure",
      "diagram"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2893",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kurabu'?",
    "Answer": "club"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2894",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kankou'?",
    "Answer": "sightseeing"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2895",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'teishutsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "presentation",
      "submission (of a report",
      "plan",
      "etc.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2896",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'irai'?",
    "Answer": "since then"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2897",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'hanareru'?",
    "Answer": "get away from"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2898",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "life",
      "living"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2899",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'character'?",
    "Answer": "seikaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2900",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'inspection'?",
    "Answer": "kensa"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2901",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shinrai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "reliance",
      "trust"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2902",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'character'?",
    "Answer": "jinbutsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2903",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'touch'?",
    "Answer": "fureru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2904",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'commemoration'?",
    "Answer": "kinen"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2905",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "role",
      "part"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2906",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'expense'?",
    "Answer": "hiyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2907",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'designation'?",
    "Answer": "shitei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2908",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanjou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "feeling",
      "emotion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2909",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kara'?",
    "Answer": [
      "emptiness",
      "hollow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2910",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kakawaru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be involved",
      "be concerned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2911",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'nakama'?",
    "Answer": [
      "comrade",
      "peer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2912",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seiri'?",
    "Answer": [
      "putting something in order",
      "sorting out"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2913",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'come to'?",
    "Answer": "itaru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2914",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'dokuritsu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "independence",
      "self-reliance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2915",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "prize",
      "award"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2916",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'birth'?",
    "Answer": "tanjou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2917",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'irassharu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "come",
      "go (honorific)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2918",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'metropolis of Tokyo'?",
    "Answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2919",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'zenin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "all members",
      "entire staff"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2920",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'clear and specific'?",
    "Answer": "meikaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2921",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sukunakutomo'?",
    "Answer": [
      "at least",
      "at a minimum"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2922",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'set'?",
    "Answer": "setto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2923",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'miryoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "charm",
      "attraction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2924",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'properly'?",
    "Answer": "kichinto"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2925",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shudan'?",
    "Answer": [
      "means",
      "way"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2926",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'effective'?",
    "Answer": "yuukou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2927",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shuuchuu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "concentration",
      "convergence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2928",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'genshou'?",
    "Answer": "phenomenon"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2929",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'to be impressed'?",
    "Answer": "kandou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2930",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'prohibition'?",
    "Answer": "kinshi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2931",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'member (of an association'?",
    "Answer": "kaiin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2932",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sugosu'?",
    "Answer": "spend (time)"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2933",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'to fully understand and accept'?",
    "Answer": "nattoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2934",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shuunyuu'?",
    "Answer": "income"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2935",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'repooto'?",
    "Answer": [
      "report",
      "paper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2936",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'age'?",
    "Answer": "nenrei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2937",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'butai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "stage",
      "setting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2938",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'traffic'?",
    "Answer": "koutsuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2939",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'other people'?",
    "Answer": "tanin"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2940",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'school class'?",
    "Answer": "kumi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2941",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'denial'?",
    "Answer": "hitei"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2942",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'handle'?",
    "Answer": "atsukau"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2943",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shuusei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "correction",
      "revision"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2944",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ichiou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "tentatively",
      "just in case"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2945",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'happen'?",
    "Answer": "shoujiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2946",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'houmon'?",
    "Answer": "visit"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2947",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'inyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "quotation",
      "citation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2948",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'art'?",
    "Answer": "geijutsu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2949",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'interpretation'?",
    "Answer": "kaishaku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2950",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'gyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "line",
      "row"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2951",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ketsuron'?",
    "Answer": "conclusion"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2952",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'difficulty'?",
    "Answer": "konnan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2953",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'recovery'?",
    "Answer": "kaifuku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2954",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'tekiyou'?",
    "Answer": [
      "application",
      "coverage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2955",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'group'?",
    "Answer": "shuudan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2956",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'situation'?",
    "Answer": "jitai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2957",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'start'?",
    "Answer": "sutaato"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2958",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sarani'?",
    "Answer": [
      "furthermore",
      "still more"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2959",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'katsuyaku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "(successful) performance",
      "action"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2960",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'life (colloquial)'?",
    "Answer": "inochi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2961",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'doctor'?",
    "Answer": "ishi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2962",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'oru'?",
    "Answer": [
      "be present",
      "stay (humble)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2963",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'appear'?",
    "Answer": "arawareru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2964",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kouen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "lecture",
      "talk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2965",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'moment'?",
    "Answer": "shunkan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2966",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'interaction'?",
    "Answer": "kouryuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2967",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'standard'?",
    "Answer": "hyoujun"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2968",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'just like'?",
    "Answer": "marude"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2969",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sutairu'?",
    "Answer": [
      "style",
      "physique"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2970",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'kanshin'?",
    "Answer": [
      "concern",
      "interest"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2971",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'take'?",
    "Answer": "toriageru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2972",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'tradition'?",
    "Answer": "dentou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2973",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'minshu'?",
    "Answer": "democracy"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2974",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'seigen'?",
    "Answer": [
      "restriction",
      "limit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2975",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'vote'?",
    "Answer": "touhyou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2976",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'mentality'?",
    "Answer": "shinri"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2977",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'about'?",
    "Answer": "daitai"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2978",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'totsuzen'?",
    "Answer": "suddenly"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2979",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'thought'?",
    "Answer": "shisou"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2980",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'answer'?",
    "Answer": "oujiru"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2981",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'lack'?",
    "Answer": "fusoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2982",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'cord'?",
    "Answer": "koodo"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2983",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'yononaka'?",
    "Answer": [
      "the world",
      "society"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2984",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'koumoku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "item",
      "topic"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2985",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'old'?",
    "Answer": "kyuu"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2986",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shidai'?",
    "Answer": "as soon as"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2987",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'long period'?",
    "Answer": "chouki"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2988",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'chosha'?",
    "Answer": [
      "author",
      "writer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2989",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'crime'?",
    "Answer": "tsumi"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2990",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'raku'?",
    "Answer": [
      "comfortable",
      "easy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2991",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'sousa'?",
    "Answer": [
      "operation",
      "manipulation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2992",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'shihai'?",
    "Answer": [
      "control",
      "rule"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2993",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'attitude'?",
    "Answer": "taido"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2994",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'katei'?",
    "Answer": [
      "process",
      "course"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2995",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'baransu'?",
    "Answer": "balance"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2996",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'continuation'?",
    "Answer": "renzoku"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2997",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'agency'?",
    "Answer": "kikan"
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2998",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the English meaning of 'ron'?",
    "Answer": [
      "argument",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "QuestionID": "Q2999",
    "Subject": "Nihongo Vocabulary",
    "Difficulty": "Easy",
    "QuestionType": "Identification",
    "Question": "What is the Romaji for 'island'?",
    "Answer": "tou"
  }
]